<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Hacks On Tap</title><link>https://audioboom.com/channels/5050689-hacks-on-tap</link><description>When David Axelrod and Mike Murphy get together to talk politics, it’s not academic. They speak from the perspective gained through hundreds of campaigns for offices from City Hall to the White House. So if you want to know what’s really going on behind the scenes, where strategic decisions are being made, pull up a stool for Hacks on Tap. Incisive, sometimes uproarious and always entertaining, these political warhorses and their guests will give you insights you’ll only get from folks who have spent a lifetime in the political trenches of both parties.</description><item><title>Groundwork &amp; Gruntwork (with Steve Israel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by the coolest cat from Congress, Steve Israel! The Hacks discuss Trump’s immigration war, avoiding the Schumer shutdown, warrior mentality, and more. Plus, stick around ‘til the end for an inspiring message from Steve—you’ll be glad you did!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 01:02:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8691139.mp3?modified=1742415270&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Recession Will Be Televised (with Doug Sosnik)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks are back, and so is the economy’s latest identity crisis. This week, Heilemann and Murphy are joined by veteran political strategist and former Clinton White House advisor Doug Sosnik! The Hacks break down the tariff wars, Wall Street’s reaction to Trump, the Tesla chainsaw massacre, government waste, the art of friendly media, and much more. Buckle up for some classic Hackery!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8667621.mp3?modified=1741735675&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Blitzkrieg of Bullsh*t</title><description>&lt;div&gt;It’s Hack to the future (but worse!) Three bleary-eyed Hacks assemble this morning to break down Trump’s speech—because, apparently, the laws of gravity and politics no longer apply. Axe, Murphy, and Heilemann dissect Democrats’ great appreciation for Musk, debate Elon’s possible motives, unravel a parliament of fluffers, and, of course, gold chainsaws. It’s a total and complete blabfest you won’t want to miss!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 22:52:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8664713.mp3?modified=1741215165&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Russian Roulette (with Sarah Longwell &amp; Patrick Gaspard)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Heilemann’s flying solo this week, but fear not! In the absence of Axe &amp;amp; Murphy, Heilemann is joined by two Hacks renowned for their razor-sharp analysis and impeccable wit: Sarah Longwell and Ambassador Patrick Gaspard. Together, they break down Trump’s presser with Macron, the latest in the Russia-Ukraine saga, the fine art of hiding behind empathy, Elon’s latest 4D chess move (or tantrum?), playing possum, and much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 22:18:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8659672.mp3?modified=1740521956&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Vladdy Knows Best (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Hack-a-doodle-doo! This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by a familiar face—former regular and now former Ambassador, the great Rahm Emanuel. The Hacks dive into inflation, Trump’s backchannel talks with Putin, DOGE intrusions, the kitten caucus, Eric Adams’ legal troubles, and much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:20:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8655778.mp3?modified=1739924481&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Make America Gulf Again (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Forget the Super Bowl—Trump’s Gulf of America is the real spectacle this week. Murphy and Heilemann are joined by the expert Hackeroo and savant, Jonathan Martin, to break it all down. JMart dives into his latest POLITICO piece on USAID, while the Hacks dissect Trump’s shade-throwing at JD Vance, looming court battles, Elon Musk’s latest rampage, and a whole lot of political mayhem. Buckle up!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 22:47:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8652667.mp3?modified=1739314122&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Elon and Order (with Kaitlan Collins)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In this completely normal, not-at-all bonkers week, Axe and Murphy were joined by White House expert and CNN anchor Kaitlan Collins—who is making her long-overdue Hacks debut. The Hacks break down Elon Musk’s latest antics, mouse traps for Democrats, tariffs, Trump’s cabinet scorecard, the state of the modern Democratic Party, Canada (yes, really), and the ongoing demolition of political norms.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:49:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8648679.mp3?modified=1742533314&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Death of Norms (with Robert Costa)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Murphy and Heilemann are joined by the great, pen-stained hack, Robert Costa. The Hacks dive into Trump’s first week in office, his aggressive approach to mass deportations, the political impact of his January 6th pardons, outrage exhaustion, security concerns, upcoming nomination votes, CHIPS, tariffs, and so much more. It’s an open-mic-night presidency, and we’re here to walk you through it!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 01:44:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8644617.mp3?modified=1738115105&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Tale of Two Speeches</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Three bleary eyed, unpardonable Hacks convened this morning to walk you through yesterday’s circus. They discuss Trump overconsumption, Biden’s pardons, Trumps pardons, setting expectations, the atomic clock of grifting, changing the constitution, and so much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:12:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8641136.mp3?modified=1737504826&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trending Right (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Heilemann are joined by fan favorite and all-around cool guy Jonathan Martin! The Hacks kick things off with a front-line report from Mike Murphy on the LA wildfires, unpacking the implications for the city and the state’s future. They also dive into the status of Trump’s nominees, the business world cozying up to Trump, Biden’s evolving legacy, and the escalating drama within Trump’s inner circle.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:10:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8637651.mp3?modified=1736899898&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hackzpah (with Jonathan Alter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Happy New Year, Hackeroos! Axe and Murphy rang in the new year with a journalism icon, the incomparable Jonathan Alter. Author of His Very Best: Jimmy Carter, A Life, Alter joins the Hacks to reflect on the passing of President Carter and the extraordinary legacy he leaves behind. The Hacks also delve into the Biden transition, Trump’s ongoing legal battles, what to expect from his appointments and campaign promises, and the ever-changing role of social media in our democracy—along with the responsibility social media executives bear in shaping it.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 23:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8634034.mp3?modified=1736294410&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>End of Year Hack Fest</title><description>&lt;div&gt;‘Twas a night filled with headlines, and all through the pod,&lt;br /&gt;
Not a topic was skipped—not even David’s odd plod.&lt;br /&gt;
Drones in the skies, with surveillance to show,&lt;br /&gt;
And scandals aplenty that continue to grow.&lt;br /&gt;
Trump’s lawsuits piled like stockings with care,&lt;br /&gt;
While inaugural donations danced through the air.&lt;br /&gt;
Inflation will be “slashed,” or so Trump has claimed,&lt;br /&gt;
And RFK vowed, with no hint of delay,&lt;br /&gt;
To make Big Pharma ads completely go away.&lt;br /&gt;
So gather around for sharp wit and good cheer—&lt;br /&gt;
It’s the wildest wrap-up, the last pod of the year!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 23:39:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8625555.mp3?modified=1734481717&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Ol' Razzle Dazzle (with John Anzalone)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Murphy and Heilemann were joined by expert Hack and pollster to the stars, John Anzalone. The Hacks dissect Trump’s Meet the Press interview, defy political gravity to forecast Trump’s future appointments, and ponder the fate of bipartisanship in a second Trump era. Plus, the guys tackle campaign loyalty, the screaming January 6th jail birds, and the state of the Democratic bench.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 22:05:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8622011.mp3?modified=1733868369&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pardon Politics (with Chris Christie)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Heilemann are joined by former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie! The Hacks dive into Christie’s unique insights as Donald Trump’s former Transition Team Chairman to explore what a second Trump term might look like: which cabinet picks are likely to stick, and which ones are simply Trump’s way of flipping the bird. Plus, the guys unpack the Hunter Biden pardon drama and ask Christie for his thoughts on the Kushner ambassadorship—an ironic twist, given their history.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 23:53:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8618736.mp3?modified=1733270067&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacksgiving Minnesode (Dontcha Know)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Happy Hacksgiving, Hackeroos! As Axe bastes his turkey to perfection, Murphy and Heilemann carved out time this morning to talk about the true meaning of Thanksgiving—tariffs (the world’s most romantic word), moronomics, and the latest recipe for chaos courtesy of Trump’s cabinet picks. Plus, the stuffing-filled scrum for DNC leadership.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
We’re so grateful for all of you, our faithful listeners—without you, we’d just be a bunch of turkeys talking into the void.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 21:40:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8614653.mp3?modified=1732657290&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The New Non-Normal (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by international Hack savant Jonathan Martin. The trio dives into Trump’s nomination circus, ranking his picks by sheer audacity and dissecting their broader implications. They also tackle the fight for DNC chair, the unraveling of democratic norms, and a potential political clash as wild as two tomcats in a pillowcase.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:47:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8610943.mp3?modified=1732056534&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Picking Through the Rubble</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, the Hacks report from the esteemed Institute of Politics at the University of Chicago. They sift through the aftermath of the election to analyze the strategies of both the Trump and Harris campaigns, Trump’s proposed appointments, the battle for leadership, and what these developments mean for the next four years and beyond.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 22:46:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8607506.mp3?modified=1731451655&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Election Post-Mortem</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Well folks, we have our results. Axe, Murphy, and Heilemann dive into the numbers and break down what this means for the next four years. They also explore the dynamics of both campaigns, analyzing shifting polling trends, key battleground states, and the broader political landscape to offer their insights on what the next chapter in American politics will hold.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 22:12:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8604869.mp3?modified=1731017587&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Landing the Plane</title><description>&lt;div&gt;On the eve of the election, the excitement is palpable as voters get ready to cast their ballots. The Hacks gather for one last huddle, dissecting the campaign’s vibe shift, Trump’s latest missteps, and the buzz from the new Iowa Seltzer poll. They recap the whirlwind of the past ten days and Murphy throws in a bold prediction. Tune in to find out what they’re thinking—and don’t forget to make your voice heard and vote!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:58:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8601666.mp3?modified=1730750371&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Girls v. Boys</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Happy Saturday, Hackeroos! This morning, the Hacks gathered for a pre-Election spectacular you won’t want to miss! They recorded a double minisode, diving into topics like candy a$$ draft dodgers, closing arguments, and Elon’s payolas. Plus, they explore the final paid media spots from both campaigns. Tune in for all the insights!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 20:51:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8600785.mp3?modified=1730580765&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Crazier &amp; Crazier</title><description>&lt;div&gt;With the election just a week away, the political landscape is like a reality show finale—full of drama, plot twists, and a few surprise guest stars! Axe, Murphy, and Heilemann dissect Trump’s tumultuous NYC rally, compare the enemies list versus the to-do list, explore the art of channeling the negative force, discuss Beyoncé (!), analyze Trump’s Joe Rogan interview, delve into Michelle Obama’s impassioned speech, and so much more! Listen to the end for a special celebrity mailbag question!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 22:31:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8598593.mp3?modified=1730241133&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Sprint</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Well, Hackeroos, we’re just two weeks away from the big showdown! Axe, Murphy, and Heilemann are really getting to the shaft of things as they discuss the final sprint of the Harris and Trump Campaign. The Hacks discuss Trump’s obsession with Arnold Palmer, Harris’s Fox News interview, Trump losing energy, the blue wall thesis, nose holding republicans, campaign messaging, early mail vote counts, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 20:39:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8593767.mp3?modified=1729629669&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Margin of Effort (with Ron Brownstein)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Hack-A-Doodle-Doo! We are three weeks out from election day, so Axe &amp;amp; Murphy have enlisted their favorite political whiz, Ron Brownstein, the human encyclopedia of hackfoolery! The Hacks break down the state of the race, dissect Harris’s messaging hits and misses, and explore how the popular vote, Senate, and House races could differ from the top of the ticket. They’ll introduce you to a lovely hammer-swinging couple, discuss giant magnets, layer cakes, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 21:05:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8590213.mp3?modified=1729026395&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Murder Genes &amp; Media Gymnastics (with Mike Bender)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Heilemann and Murphy were joined by the esteemed and remarkably flexible Mike Bender, NYT political correspondent and author of &lt;em&gt;Frankly, We Did Win This Election: The Inside Story of How Trump Lost&lt;/em&gt;. The Hacks break down murder genes, Harris’s media blitz, take bets on whether there will be another presidential debate, moments of crazy strength, being in the zone, wiggly flip-flopping, and so much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 21:03:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8586765.mp3?modified=1728421491&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>VP Debate</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Three bleary-eyed, bloviating Hacks convened this morning to dissect the VP debate. The Hacks leave no stone unturned, exploring everything from electric vehicle politics to eyeliner choices—because it's all fair game, as long as the leading man isn’t upstaged. Tune in to hear about manatee killer instincts, Vance’s early debate wins, Walz’s underdog finish, a slick yet sloppy tie, and so much more!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:28:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8581423.mp3?modified=1727904552&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Poller Coaster (with Alyssa Farah Griffin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined Alyssa Farah Griffin, host of The View and former Trump White House communications staffer. The Hacks dive into poll-a-palooza, viral pet songs, Trump’s internal messaging battle, radioactive candidates, and so much more. Buckle up!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 21:57:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8576593.mp3?modified=1727215101&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>It’s the Economy, Stupid (with James Carville)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by The Ragin' Cajun himself. They explored the latest political developments, including another assassination attempt on Trump, the case Kamala Harris and her team need to make, and a thorough analysis of the economy and Bidenomics. They also previewed the upcoming documentary that chronicles Carville’s career and the battles he’s fought—because if anyone knows how to tell a legendary story, it’s Carville!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:15:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8571926.mp3?modified=1726532209&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Debate Post Mortem</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In a caffeine-fueled fever dream, three overworked faux doctors gathered this morning to dissect last night’s presidential debate. Join us as our "medical experts" administer a thorough post-mortem on the debate’s highs and lows: from the subtle art of baiting former presidents to whether your furry friends are in danger from political shrapnel. We’ll also diagnose the hot-button issues, dissect the theatrical stagecraft, and predict the political fallout with a dose of diagnostic wit.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:18:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8569550.mp3?modified=1726093163&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Debate Preview</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This morning the Hacks gathered bright and early just for you, to dish out a can’t-miss debate preview. As the post-convention sugar high fades and a fresh New York Times poll shakes up the race, the Hacks dive into the high-stakes drama of the upcoming debate. They break down how each camp is gearing up for the spotlight, what we can expect from the moderators, and much more. Plus, in a truly scientific endeavor, the guys offer their highly precise, definitely-not-just-a-guess estimates on TV audience size. Don’t miss it!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:15:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8568151.mp3?modified=1725905766&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Fuster Cluck</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Happy post-Labor Day campaign sprint to all who celebrate! The Hacks gathered this morning to dissect the Harris &amp;amp; Walz interview, figure out who's taken the toughest swings at Mike Pence, and take a deep dive into how abortion might shake up this election. They also discuss Trump’s struggle to stay on message, his strong man schtick, the battle for Pennsylvania, and cross pollinating between swing states. And in true Trump fashion, they’ve got an announcement that’s not just exciting—it’s tremendous, beautiful, and the best you’ve ever seen. Believe me!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 23:59:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8565533.mp3?modified=1725408074&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mainstream v. Extreme</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This bleary-eyed morning, the Hacks gathered to dish out their final takes on the Democratic National Convention. They tackled Kamala’s speech, Trump’s misdialed thoughts on Kamala’s speech, where the campaigns go from here, RFK dropping out, Chicago being an extraordinary host city, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:07:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8560566.mp3?modified=1724443720&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Overtime Oration</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks are LIVE from the iconic Chicago institution, Manny’s Deli! Join Axe, Heilemann, and Murphy as they dig into Biden’s speeches—yes, both of them—and take a deep dive into the highs and lows of the other speakers' performances. They’ll be serving up hot takes—make that hot latkes—on filibustering, whether the messaging hit the mark, and, of course, how many times Murphy plans to cast his vote while he's in the Windy City. And don’t miss their special segment where they debate if a good corned beef can save a bad policy!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 22:45:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8559006.mp3?modified=1724193995&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Rule of Three</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Murphy kick off this week's episode with an exciting announcement that’s sure to shake things up! After the big reveal, they dive into Trump’s glitchy X interview, the evolving role of social media in this election cycle and what it means for the future of politics, check in on polling, Kamalamentum, and Walz Weirdness. With the DNC convention headed to our beloved Chicago, the guys share their thoughts on what to expect.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:50:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8555634.mp3?modified=1723589479&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Ope There It Is (with John Anzalone)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;*Disclaimer: The Executive Producer of this podcast is from the great state of Minnesota.*&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This oh for cute week Axe and Murphy were joined by the great John Anzalone. In exciting but not at all predictable news, Minnesota has once again produced a Vice Presidential candidate. The Hacks discuss how Minnesota is the best state in the union, dontcha know, Walz’s unparalleled experience with state (a)fairs, how the campaign is pivoting to build the Wal(l)z messaging, and how the announcement could (purple) rain on Trump’s parade. Can the man from 10,000 lakes rise up to meet these high stakes as he enters skol-ding hot waters? Grab a pop, and a Juicy Lucy, and tune in!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:18:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8552481.mp3?modified=1722996095&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Veepstakes (with Jonathan Martin and Bob Costa)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Murphy was joined by Mr. Politics, Bob Costa, and Politico reporter and current flâneur in Paris, Jonathan Martin. The Hacks dive into the vice presidential contenders, the Biden-to-Harris transition relay, the race to put new ads on the air, and Donald Trump's messaging hurdles against his new opponent. And naturally, our very own Mike Murphy clinches the gold medal for his spot-on Hacks on Tap prediction&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 21:07:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8549155.mp3?modified=1722373718&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Kamalat (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by expert Hackeroo and high-velocity pundit, John Heilemann. Because clearly, there's just not enough breaking news happening in the world. The Hacks salute Joe Biden’s decision, and dive into the next steps of the Kamala Harris presidential campaign: Inheriting the Biden operation, coming out with new messaging and ads, reversing the Biden age issue, and who could be the Vice President’s Vice President? The Hacks also cover “brat,” campaign attack ads, inflation, the border, Dobbs, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8545878.mp3?modified=1721771958&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Fight (with Tim Alberta)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by esteemed journalist, Republican chronicler, and author Tim Alberta. Together, they dive into an incredibly significant and historic news cycle, covering the shocking attempted assassination of a former president, the opening night of the Republican National Convention, Trump's VP pick and protégé, classified documents, political shifts, strength versus weakness, legacy politics, and much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:10:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8542592.mp3?modified=1721171463&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Press Panic (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, famous elitists Axe Murphy donned their velvet suits to catch up with fellow elite Hack and friend of the pod, Bill Kristol. The Hacks dive into Biden’s path forward, the growing significance of Kamala Harris and her future ambitions, Trump’s veepstakes, backup contenders, White House press shenanigans, campaign leaks, political backstabbing, and more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:45:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8538715.mp3?modified=1720557936&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Tick Tock, Tick Tock (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by provocateur, world traveler, food &amp;amp; wine expert, and nationally ranked ballroom dancer, Jonathan Martin. The guys breakdown the post debate political landscape in the public and behind closed doors, check in on a few key states, and prepare for a new batch of polls. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:19:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8533812.mp3?modified=1719951561&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Political Fairway (with David Plouffe)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Murphy teed off bright and early this morning to putt heads with David Plouffe. We had a pre-debate chat with him and wanted to regroup to compare-and-contrast notes. The Hacks drive straight into last night's debate: the overall outcome, the impact of no audience and mic cuts, which VP candidate landed a hole-in-one, sidestepping tough questions like a sand trap, and a whole lot more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:25:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8532141.mp3?modified=1719602731&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Trap (with David Plouffe)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by the legendary Hack and campaign maestro, David Plouffe. The Davids and Mike delve deep into the upcoming debate and how the campaigns are preparing. Who will poke first, big red forehead buttons, viral moments, cut mics, counter punching, pivoting, baiting, and the ultimate traps. The Hacks also map out the best case, worst case, and just-get-through-it scenarios for both the Biden and Trump camps. Get ready for an insider’s guide to the debate stage!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 22:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8529830.mp3?modified=1719354096&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Naked On A Rock (with Jonathan Freedland)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by Guardian columnist Jonathan Freedland, who also hosts the Guardian's "Politics Weekly America" podcast and co-hosts the Unholy podcast. The Hacks discuss debate preparation: microphone logistics and optics, messaging from convicted felons, and playing checkers with Charles Manson. In this international edition of Hacks on Tap, they hop across the pond to discuss UK politics and weather, and then talk about Israel and what to expect from Netanyahu’s visit to the U.S. Plus, we celebrate one of our very own in-house Hacks!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:18:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8526040.mp3?modified=1718752701&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Double Haters (with Sarah Longwell)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by focus group guru and Bulwark legend, Sarah Longwell. Trump is out of the courtroom and back on the trail, the Hacks break down his concerns over teleprompter technology, Hunter Biden’s conviction, how both camps are preparing for the debate, vibe sessions v. recessions, dancing bears, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8521960.mp3?modified=1718143166&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Guilties (with Mark McKinnon &amp; Steve Israel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Murphy is flying solo, so he brought in A-team Hackeroos and frequent guests Mark McKinnon and Steve Israel. The Hacks discuss Trump’s 34 guilty verdicts and how both sides should adjust their messaging, what this means for undecided voters, the second big polling panic, the upcoming debate worth all the marbles, the Trump VP candidate smell test, pop vs. soda, and so so so much more. You won’t want to miss this one!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:59:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8518454.mp3?modified=1717541957&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Angry Trump (with Chris Christie)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by former New Jersey governor and recent GOP presidential hopeful, Chris Christie! The Hacks draw on Christie’s experience preparing Trump for past debates to discuss his mindset heading into the Biden debate, his legal saga and fear of jail, Nikki Haley’s endorsement, being the adult in the room, leaf blowers, surrogates, and much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8512671.mp3?modified=1716936620&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Wetting the Bed (with Howard Wolfson)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by the legendary Hack and master strategist, Howard Wolfson. The Hacks delve into Trump's legal troubles: where are they headed, and do voters care? They compare the Biden and Trump campaign financing reports, preview the June presidential debate, discuss foreign policy issues, and reveal Mike Murphy's pop culture presence.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:53:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8509053.mp3?modified=1716332038&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>W.T.F., Man? (With John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Gibbs were joined by one of our esteemed Hackeroos, a favorite among all-stars, none other than John Heilemann. Together, they delve into various topics, including the rotating cast of characters in court with Donald Trump, the latest poll findings from the New York Times, economic trends and the rising cost of living, as well as the ongoing conflicts in the Middle East, plus so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:09:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8505213.mp3?modified=1715728189&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Floors &amp; Ceilings (with Doug Sosnik)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by an expert Hackeroo, Doug Sosnik, former Senior Advisor to President Bill Clinton. the Hacks discuss Trump’s legal antics, Big Campaign Energy (BCE), puppy slayers, the race for GOP VP, RFK’s unbaked cake, escape valves, capitalism, and so much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:29:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8501810.mp3?modified=1715120970&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Tired, Sleepy &amp; Gassy (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Murphy and Gibbs were joined by the great Paul Begala, CNN contributor and former counselor to President Bill Clinton. The Hacks discuss the White House Correspondents Dinner, Trump’s ongoing legal issues, CNN’s newest poll, unconventional media opportunities, shooting puppies(???), and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:32:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8498387.mp3?modified=1714512792&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bubbling Over (with Scott Jennings)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by Scott Jennings, a GOP strategist, conservative columnist, and CNN commentator. The Hacks discuss Johnson’s Speakership and the battle to pass aid packages, star GOP recruits, foreign wars, campus free speech, Biden’s messaging, and Trump’s trials.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 23:46:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8494991.mp3?modified=1713916004&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bad Options (with Whit Ayers and Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week finds Gibbs flying solo as Axe and Murphy are, shall we say, on the run. Nevertheless, the show must go on, and Gibbs is joined by two esteemed guests: GOP pollster Whit Ayers and Jonathan Martin, renowned author of “This Will Not Pass: Trump, Biden and the Battle for America’s Future". Together, they embark on a deep dive into the week's tumultuous news cycle, examining everything from the latest New York Times poll to Trump’s hush money jury selection, the challenges and opportunities for both parties on abortion and immigration messaging, foreign policy, campaign infrastructure, margins of error, the golden bachelor, and so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:42:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8491576.mp3?modified=1713307374&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mixed Messages (with Sasha Issenberg)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by the distinguished Hack and renowned lie detective, Sasha Issenberg. Together, they delve into Trump's contradictory stance on abortion and his intriguing status as a Florida voter. The Hacks also dissect Biden's endeavors for student loan forgiveness, the evolving landscape of TikTok, the complexities of foreign policy, ongoing conflicts, the impact of social media, the rise of deep fakes, the lunar eclipse, and oh so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8488290.mp3?modified=1719118906&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Gas &amp; Eggs (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe &amp;amp; Murphy were joined by a fan favorite Hackeroo, the great John Heilemann. The guys discussed Biden’s three presidents event, Trump’s holiday messaging, campaign financing, margins of error, debates, gag orders, hush money, porn stars, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 22:57:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8482805.mp3?modified=1718514119&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bizarroland (with Bakari Sellers)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The week Axe and Murphy were joined by Bakari Sellers, a former South Carolina State Rep, current attorney, and political commentator—making his debut appearance on Hacks on Tap! The Hacks discussed the propitious time we find ourselves in (bet you can’t guess who chose that word), Trump as a Showman, recent polls and their contextual significance, one-party rule, running against the couch, as well as knives, forks, and geometry. And, of course, so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 23:41:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8479283.mp3?modified=1717909342&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Nostalgia for Normalcy (with Maggie Haberman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Gibbs and Murphy were joined by the scoop-master Hackeroo extraordinaire Maggie Haberman, who is the Senior Political Correspondent for the New York Times and author of “Confidence Man: The Making of Donald Trump and the Breaking of America”. The Hacks discuss Trump’s colorful rally in Dayton, the Ohio Senate race, Biden’s messaging problems and opportunities, and so much more. Tune in for the brilliant analysis, listen all the way through for all of Murphy’s insider gossip.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:44:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8475894.mp3?modified=1710884684&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Dingbats with Chainsaws (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy were joined by the immortal and excellent Amy Walter, publisher, and editor-in-chief of The Cook Report with Amy Walter. The Hacks discuss Biden’s State of the Union speech and Katie Britt’s rebuttal. The guys also delve into discuss the state of the race, new campaign ads, the Trump Lobotomy Academy, guys in suits yelling at each other, loyalty purges and fun house mirrors. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:57:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8472546.mp3?modified=1716786130&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Sore Bruiser (with Jen Psaki and Scott Jennings)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Murray and Gibbs took off on vacation, their absence becoming our gain, as Axe welcomed two powerhouse Hackeroos, along with familiar faces Jen Psaki and Scott Jennings. The Hacks delve into the aftermath of Super Tuesday, Haley's exit and its impact on the race, the art of acceptance speeches, effective messaging strategies, weird-ass campaigns, the ever-relevant sore loser rule, and the delicate dance of punching down. Plus, they peer into their crystal ball to speculate on what Biden's SOTU speech may focus on.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8469558.mp3?modified=1716181335&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Politicianing (with Sarah Longwell)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Gibbs had the pleasure of welcoming the illustrious Superstar Hackeroo and cherished friend of the pod, Sarah Longwell, who is the host of The Focus Group Podcast and publisher of The Bulwark. Together, the Hacks embark on a riveting exploration of the convoluted narratives surrounding the South Carolina primary, the tumultuous state of the GOP, the enigmatic campaign landscape in Michigan, Biden's political quagmires, Trumped-up allegations, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 23:07:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8465249.mp3?modified=1715490114&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Main Character Energy (with Steve Israel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by former congressman and savant Steve Israel. The Hacks dissect the adventures of the world's most 'useful idiot' on his escapade to Russia, explore the sneaker culture at Sneaker Con (pun intended), draw insights from the NY-03 race and the Suozzi blueprint, delve into the realm of kitchen table issues, speculate on potential State of the Union topics, savor some nerd food, marvel at Tim Scott's miraculous flexibility in flipping his moral stances faster than a pancake, and pay homage to the late hero, Alexei Navalny. Remember, democracy isn't merely bestowed upon us; it's a continual project in which we must all actively participate.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:16:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8460958.mp3?modified=1716181329&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Riding the Dragon (with Kasie Hunt)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by CNN Anchor and Chief National Affairs Analyst, the brilliant Kasie Hunt! The Hacks discuss Biden’s age, his tumultuous press conference last week, falling into the orchestra pit, the new Michigan, immigration bill negotiations, Trump’s geopolitical antics, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:25:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8457531.mp3?modified=1715662943&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Cynicism on Steroids (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Gibbs and Murphy were graced with the presence of Jonathan Martin, the senior political columnist for Politico and a Sublime Hackeroo. The trio delves into Nevada (pronunciation to be disputed), Nikki, four-digit numbers, Biden’s surrogate campaign, robot campaigns, five-alarm fires, desk chairs on the Titanic, Schoolhouse Rock, calculating double crazy, everything primary, everything polling, everything everywhere, all at once, and also so much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:08:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8454009.mp3?modified=1715058108&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Under His Skin</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Axe and Murphy were joined by Jonathan Karl, ABC News’s chief Washington correspondent and co-anchor of This Week with George Stephanopoulos. The Hacks delve into the intricacies of Nikki Haley's campaign, Trump's unpredictable nature, the unique dynamics of campaigning from courthouses, the importance of reasonableness, chess with irate chimpanzees, bone spurs, bingo bango bongo, and so much more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:36:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8449577.mp3?modified=1714453307&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>It’s Not Over…?</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, the Hacks gathered to delve into the results and implications of the New Hampshire primary, decoding their significance for the upcoming 2024 political landscape. In his usual fashion, Trump pivots his ire towards Nikki Haley. Biden’s campaign begins stepping up its game, preparing for another battle with Trump. And, most importantly, our beloved Mike Murphy has a special announcement!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8445119.mp3?modified=1713934893&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Shiniest Silver Medal</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs convene to discuss the aftermath of the Iowa Caucus. Murphy, our boots-on-the-ground maestro, serves up firsthand accounts from the caucus battlegrounds. While Axe and Gibbs dissect Biden’s messaging problem. The Hacks also discuss crow burgers, building momentum, the romance of politics, what’s cooking in the other early states, dancing bears, tiny knives, and cracked crystal balls. The Hacks also walk the political prediction plank when discussing New Hampshire.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 23:10:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8433417.mp3?modified=1705446678&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Post Debate Hacknalysis (Another One!)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week our trio of seasoned hacks dives headfirst into the CNN debate, mourns Chris Christie's campaign exit, and anticipates the Iowa Caucus outcomes. The gloves are off as Nikki Haley and DeSantis enter a political brawl, while Trump's town hall takes center stage. Our hacks offer sharp insights on Iowa's weather, candidates' dance moves, and the political intricacies of the great states of Iowa, New Hampshire, and South Carolina. Tune in for a whirlwind tour of the week's political rollercoaster, because when it comes to politics, laughter is the ultimate survival strategy.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:31:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8428970.mp3?modified=1712811699&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Trumpire Strikes Back (with Kristen Soltis Anderson)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In the run-up to the Iowa Caucus, Axe and Murphy were joined by expert Republican pollster Kristen Soltis Anderson. The Hacks dive into polling, discuss Nikki Haley’s blunder, the battle for second in Iowa, the promise of New Hampshire, blimps, blemishes, ugly zippers, and large orange marbles.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:13:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8424354.mp3?modified=1712034091&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Dictator for a Day</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy convened for their final episode of the year! The Hacks discuss recent polling, the upcoming Iowa Caucus and New Hampshire Primary, the one man Biden campaign, singing off a song sheet, Hunter Biden’s legal troubles, and the battle to be the new lion. Plus, the guys make their 2024 predictions. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 01:04:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8415537.mp3?modified=1710219741&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Post Debate Hacknalysis</title><description>&lt;div&gt;We’ve kept you waiting long enough - here is the post debate Hacknalysis with your pals David Axelrod and Robert Gibbs. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:56:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8413111.mp3?modified=1709701292&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Eyes on Iowa (with Adam Nagourney)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by ink stained Hack, Adam Nagourney. Adam is a political reporter for the New York Times and author of “The Times: How the Newspaper of Record Survived Scandal, Scorn, and the Transformation of Journalism”.  The Hacks discuss the upcoming Iowa caucus, the battle brewing between Haley and DeSantis, the cost of Thanksgiving, messages from presidents past, eating crow, and slicing the salami a little too thin. Plus, Murphy dabbles in ventriloquism.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:09:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8408111.mp3?modified=1709010156&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacksgiving</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Murphy have a special Hacksgiving message for you!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:07:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8404515.mp3?modified=1700600870&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Circus Show (with Mark McKinnon and John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Circus comes to town, literally, as the guys are joined by Mark McKinnon and John Heilemann, who created Showtime’s beloved show “The Circus.” The Hacks clown around while juggling a variety of topics, ranging from Biden’s acrobatics around recent poll numbers, Joe Manchin’s disappearing act, the elephants walking on a tight rope (and dropping off it), and Trump’s hare pulling. Tune in for even more puns, and even better analysis!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:18:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8400707.mp3?modified=1707714145&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Ship Show</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs convened in the middle of the night to discuss the third GOP debate. The Hacks talk about the winners, the losers, and the battle for second in the Iowa caucus. Tune in to hear them discuss abortion messaging, dime store trump ideas, the royal we, panic polls, losers, and borscht sh!t. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 21:20:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8398243.mp3?modified=1707282144&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Chaos, Vendettas &amp; Drama (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by the inimitable and unbelievable superstar Hackeroo Jonathan Martin. JMart is a senior reporter at POLITICO, and co-author of “This Will Not Pass: Trump, Biden, and the Battle for America’s Future”. The guys break down the new Iowa poll, talk about who is up and who is down, Trump’s power in the GOP, the new Speaker of the House, Pence’s French vanilla problem, Dean Phillips, Israel and Palestine, the UAW strike, chat GPT speeches, and somehow so much more! Tune in! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:49:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8393338.mp3?modified=1698792646&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Congressional Clown Show (with Scott Jennings)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by Scott Jennings, a GOP strategist, conservative columnist, and CNN commentator. The Hacks pull back the circus curtains to reveal what’s going on behind the scenes in the speakers battle. The guys discuss the potential candidates, the relationship building across factions, role of democrats, and the commentary from the peanut gallery. The Hacks also discuss border security, Ukraine and Israel funding, Biden’s positioning on Israel, potential presidential Democratic challengers, Trump’s legal woes and plea deals. Plus the guys visit fantasy island while answering your mailbag questions!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 22:41:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8389770.mp3?modified=1705899750&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Riding Indictments (with John Harwood)</title><description>This week Axe and Murphy were joined by the great John Harwood! Fresh off his ProPublica interview with President Biden, Harwood joined the Hacks in discussing Trump’s ongoing legal drama, the future of the GOP, the politics of old men yelling at clouds, the essential role of the Speaker and the battle for it, Biden’s trip to Israel, FEC reports, unleashing dogs, and dancing on termites!</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:53:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8385961.mp3?modified=1705295059&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Loser’s Lament (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by one of the greatest Hacks in all of the land, Amy Walter, who is the publisher and editor-in-chief of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter. The Hacks discuss the Israel-Hamas war, Nikki Haley’s rising status and her foreign policy expertise, FEC reports, Biden’s economic numbers, Ukraine funding, the battle for the Speakership, independent candidate chaos, and so much more. Tune in for the political insight, stay through the whole episode to hear Murphy write/perform a jingle for Biden. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:38:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8382360.mp3?modified=1704690149&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Fight Within The Fight (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This messy week we have a lot to cover: McCarthy’s battle with Gaetz, the nearly averted shutdown, the great aftermath of the second GOP debate, California Senate — so much stuff we had to bring in the inimitable Jonathan Martin. You may know him from his writing in POLITICO or his classes at Harvard! Make sure to tune in to hear about skullduggery, vendettas, psychic nutritionist political advisors, and so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 23:40:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8378163.mp3?modified=1704085566&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Post Debate Hacknalysis</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Late last night, despite all three Hacks feeling a little bit dumber, the guys convened to record a special post debate Hacks on Tap. The Hacks declare their debate winners and losers, and predict who will be on the next debate stage. They also break down Newsom’s new strides, picket line politics, flip floppery, and battery powered boats. Don’t Donald Duck up and skip this episode, it’s a good one! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8375702.mp3?modified=1703653329&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Dancing Bear Theory (with Sarah Longwell)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by Sarah Longwell, publisher of The Bulwark and host of The Focus Group podcast. The Hacks discuss the upcoming GOP debate, the difficulties and nuances of interviewing Trump, DeSantis and Haley’s viability, aging presidents, nailing jello to walls, and clowns with flame throwers. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Want to hear more from Sarah Longwell? Make sure to listen to The Focus Group podcast, new episodes will be coming out on Saturday!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8371109.mp3?modified=1702962148&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pony Faced Cowboys (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Gibbs &amp;amp; Murphy were joined by the great Bill Kristol, who is editor-at-large of The Bulwark. The Hacks discuss Bidens overseas trip, the role of the media, Republicans opening up an impeachment inquiry, and presidential polling around impeachment past. Plus the guys look into their Kristol ball and preview the next GOP debate. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 22:37:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8366310.mp3?modified=1702270948&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Talk A Little Louder (with Jeff Zeleny)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by Jeff Zeleny, who is the Chief National Affairs Correspondent for CNN. Jeff gives an update on what he has seen on the road in New Hampshire, the Hacks then break down Biden’s communication challenges, new poll numbers and the battle for the GOP nomination. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 21:55:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8362670.mp3?modified=1701666151&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The MAGA Hymn Book (with Scott Jennings)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by Scott Jennings, a GOP strategist, conservative columnist, and CNN commentator. The Hacks discuss Trump’s most recent presidential portrait, his upcoming trial, and how this could impact the nominating process. The guys also talk about pre/post-Trump GOP candidates, post GOP debate performances, identify politics, Biden’s campaign performance, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:50:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8358770.mp3?modified=1693349513&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Haley’s Comet</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The bleary-eyed Hacks convened early this morning to discuss the first GOP debate of the 2024 election and the poll vaulting nature of politics. The guys bloviate about Trump’s absence, Nikki’s breakthrough performance, Ramaswamy’s rising poll numbers, and the candidate responses on abortion, supporting Trump, and January 6th. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8356403.mp3?modified=1700629327&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>May The Fourth Indictment Be With You</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Did you miss us? Well, we missed you so much that we decided to convene all three Hacks this week. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy discuss Trump’s most recent indictment, the guys preview the upcoming GOP debate, set the scene for the Iowa Caucus and New Hampshire Primary, and discuss Hunter Biden’s legal woes. Plus, Murphy gives a dispatch from his hammock in New Hampshire. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 23:25:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8350497.mp3?modified=1699851756&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Costa La Vista (with Robert Costa)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Robert Costa, the chief election and campaign correspondent for CBS news, joined Axe and Murphy to discuss the great pageantry of democracy. The Hacks discuss GOP polling and spending, knocking out frontrunners, unprecedented indictments, DeSantis DeSinking, escape valves, medals for democracy, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 22:41:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8340315.mp3?modified=1698037356&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Indict-Me-Not (with Dana Bash)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This bonkers news week Axe and Gibbs were joined by CNN’s chief political correspondent and anchor of “Inside Politics”. Dana walks us through the newest Trump indictment news, and the Hacks pick her brain on Trump’s messaging, what the indictments mean for 2024, and how the American people will serve as his jury. The Hacks also talk about Manchin campaigning in New Hampshire, Chris Christie qualifying for the GOP debate, Biden’s performance, Pence’s appeal, Faustian bargains, losers, cowards, chickens, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:31:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8336951.mp3?modified=1697518927&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Show Me Your Strategy (with Heidi Heitkamp)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by former North Dakota Senator and current Director of the Institute of Politics at the University of Chicago, Heidi Heitkamp! The Hacks discuss DeSantis’s bet on Iowa and his courtship of Kim Reynolds, the flipping of abortion as a political issue, Super PAC ads, fundraising number, rural messaging, and the crickets from Biden’s presidential campaign. Plus Heidi gives some Fargo wisdom to her governor and Murphy sneaks in a Gina Raimondo plug!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:11:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8333560.mp3?modified=1696914136&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mailbag Spectacular K Mart Special</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Murphy and Gibbs bumped a few former presidents to celebrate their favorite holiday by answering YOUR questions! The guys bloviate about Bidenomics, Enron accounting, chickens in tuxedos, Kevin’s caucus politics, Supreme Court rulings, and supremely delicious political food festivities! Tune in and happy forth to you all!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8327612.mp3?modified=1696222938&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>To Be Determined (with James Carville &amp; Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe was joined by living political legend/greatest Hack of all time James Carville and hat model/co-host of The Circus/also an amazing Hack Mark McKinnon. The guys discuss Christie’s post Covid vendetta against Trump, GOP field elimination and late entries, Trump’s leaked audio, DeSantis’ charisma problem, post-Roe politics, No Labels, breaking glass, and so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:56:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8324733.mp3?modified=1695704533&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Golf Shirts, Pants, and Top Secret Documents (with Maggie Haberman and Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Gibbs chats this week with the incomparable and always informative Maggie Haberman of the New York Times and Jonathan Martin of Politico. The Hacks discuss Trump’s indictment, his political and legal strategy (spoiler alert they’re the same), his Fox News interview, and whether or not he will participate in the GOP debates. They also discuss the primary challenges facing his GOP opponents, Hunter Biden’s charges, third party challengers to Biden, and Joe Manchin’s boat.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8321057.mp3?modified=1695013330&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Typhoon from Trenton (with Doug Heye)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by the Swiss Army Knife of political insight, Doug Heye. Doug taps into his experience as the former communications director for the RNC and deputy chief of staff to Eric Cantor to discuss the immediate term, long term, and short term repercussions of Trump’s second indictment, Chris Christie’s CNN Town Hall, DeSantis finding his lane, McCarthy’s negotiations/struggles with the freedom caucus, and so much more&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8317022.mp3?modified=1694494928&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>And They’re Off (with Jeff Zeleny)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by a new (but already a favorite) Hack, Jeff Zeleny, who is the Chief National Affairs Correspondent for CNN. Jeff gives an update on what he has seen on the road in Iowa, the Hacks then breakdown the state of the GOP race, who they expect to qualify for the upcoming debate(s), and if Trump should even participate and why he probably will. Then the Hacks, aspiring cowboys, plan a trip to North Dakota! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:50:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8313022.mp3?modified=1693890128&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Deal or No Deal (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Murphy and Gibbs were joined by the man who wears many hats, both literally and figuratively, Mark McKinnon of Showtime’s “The Circus”. The Hacks break down the debt ceiling negotiations, what cat herding and goat rodeos are going on behind the scenes, the GOP race for the White House, DeSantis v. Trump, and also DeSantis v. technology. Plus, Murphy plays around with ChatGPT during the listener mailbag.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:15:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8309472.mp3?modified=1685496503&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Rocket Fuel… Or Not (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by Super Hackeroo and CNN Contributor Paul Begala. The Hacks discuss Tim Scott’s announcement, the battle for the GOP primary, debt ceiling (default) negotiations, the x-factor that is the candidate gene, the No Labels Party, Mount Rushmore politicians, gold toilets, and refreshing smiles! Plus so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 22:13:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8305676.mp3?modified=1692594153&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Bear Minimum (with Joe Scarborough)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by former politician and current Hack Joe Scarborough, who is the co-host of “Morning Joe” on MSNBC.  The guys talk about Trump fatigue, the battle for the GOP nomination, the political earthquake that was the Dobbs decision, upcoming tremors, the danger of being too cautious, and so much more! Pull up a stool, pour a cold one, and tune in! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:04:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8302122.mp3?modified=1692075764&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Aerogenous Events (with Sarah Longwell)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Expert Hack Sarah Longwell, publisher of The Bulwark and host of The Focus Group podcast, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the state of the 2024 presidential race. The Hacks also break down debt ceiling negotiations, discuss DeSantis’ meta strategy and if he has ever met-a-voter, invent a new word, and oh so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:10:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8298210.mp3?modified=1691470972&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Fig Leaf or Full Monty (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by a superstar Hackeroo, the formidable Amy Walter, who is the publisher and editor-in-chief of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter. Amy joined Axe and Murphy to discuss the debt ceiling negotiations, Trump fatigue, big Senate announcements and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 23:49:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8293979.mp3?modified=1683071445&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Tuckered Out (with Jen Psaki)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Murphy and Gibbs were joined by guest genius Jen Psaki who is host of MSNBC’s “Inside with Jen Psaki” on Sundays at 12 p.m. ET and the former White House Press Secretary for President Joe Biden. The Hacks breakdown the recent CNN and Fox News talent oustings, review Biden’s announcement video, and discuss the GOP primary battle. Plus the hacks are joined, yet again, by our trusted veteran hack road correspondent. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 01:37:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8287841.mp3?modified=1682536765&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pudding Politics (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by expert Hack and political Scribe Jonathan Martin of POLITICO. The Hacks review GOP primary attack ads, discuss the rollercoaster that is DeSantis’ feud with Disney, break down Diane Feinstein’s Senate absence and what this could mean for the battle for her seat, and Murphy goes on a trip to Iowa!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 23:01:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8283740.mp3?modified=1681858983&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Out-Trumping Trump (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Murphy were joined by their favorite guest Hack, John Heilemann, of Showtime’s The Circus. The guys talk about Biden’s history of slow walking, the DNC announcement that the 2024 convention will be in the great city of Chicago (not that any of the Hacks are biased), the expulsion of two of the Tennessee Three, and how the GOP presidential contenders can be successful beyond Trump. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 23:47:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8279354.mp3?modified=1681256921&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Stormy Tuesday (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This uneventful week Murphy and Gibbs were joined by gentleman Hack Paul Begala to discuss the first ever criminal indictment of a U.S. President. The Hacks break down the indictment, Trump’s surrender, and his speech. Plus the Hacks are joined by their Midwestern correspondent to dive into the Chicago Mayor’s race as well as the Wisconsin Supreme Court Race. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8276367.mp3?modified=1680739120&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Premature Indictment Excitement? (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined by Mark McKinnon of Showtime’s “The Circus” to talk about the latest three-ring political spectacle. The Hacks break down Trump's most recent legal battles and give a campaign trail update. And in light of another horrific school shooting they talk about the politics of gun safety legislation. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 23:18:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8272383.mp3?modified=1680131969&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump Trouble in River City: A Deep Dive Into The IA GOP Caucus (With David Kochel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Gibbs and Murphy were joined by Mr. Iowa himself, super hack extraordinaire David Kochel. The Hacks address the indictment incitement (and excitement) looming over Manhattan, how Trump and his GOP friends and foes are responding, and how this will impact the 2024 election. Plus the Hacks dive deep into the cornfields of Iowa and discuss the upcoming caucus, the advantages and disadvantages for the current slate of GOP candidates, and of course the Iowa State Fair butter cow.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 22:28:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8267827.mp3?modified=1679437760&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Orange Caligula (with Charlie Sykes)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Charlie Sykes, Editor at Large of The Bulwark, host of the Bulwark Podcast, and author of “How the Right Lost Its Mind” joined Axe and Murphy to talk about the SVB bank crisis, the politics of bailouts, debt ceiling and budget negotiations, we check in on the Republicans on the campaign trail, and they look ahead to what all of this means for 2024, and beyond!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8264002.mp3?modified=1678834279&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Payback Playbook (with Maggie Haberman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by Maggie Haberman, a senior political correspondent for the New York Times and a legendary reporter, to discuss all things Trump v. DeSantis. The Hacks break down their dueling speeches, mixed messages, loyalty pledges, nicknames, insults, and so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 22:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8259515.mp3?modified=1678227151&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Woke Wars (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by a superstar Hackeroo, the formidable Amy Walter, who is the publisher and editor-in-chief of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter. Amy joined Axe and Gibbs (Murphy was busy voting in Chicago) to discuss the DeSantis book tour, Trump’s standing in the Republican Party, the Michigan Senate race, and what and when to expect results from the Chicago Mayor’s race. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Plus David previews his Axe Files interview with Peter Meijer.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 22:30:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8255339.mp3?modified=1677623498&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Three Dimensional Vulcan Chess (with Doug Heye)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by Hackeroo (and very friendly guy) Doug Heye. Doug taps into his experience as the former communications director for the RNC and deputy chief of staff to Eric Cantor to discuss the 2024 primary field, Biden’s recent trip to Ukraine, and how age will factor into both Biden and Trump’s next steps. The Hacks also dive into the Midwest and look at a Wisconsin Supreme Court Race and the Chicago Mayor’s race.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:16:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8251267.mp3?modified=1677025479&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Medicare, Medicare, Medicare (with Steve Israel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Former Congressman and chair of the DCCC Steve Israel joins Axe and Murphy for our duo Valentines Day and 200th episode special(!) to discuss the all the hot air over spy balloons, social security as a campaign message, Trump vs. DeSantis, and honestly, Trump vs. Everyone.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:06:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8247486.mp3?modified=1676419681&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>State Of The SOTU</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Three bleary-eyed Hacks convene to discuss Biden’s State of the Union address. Axe and Gibbs reflect on their experience in crafting SOTU speeches and the various special interests that you have to navigate. The Hacks also break down Biden’s acuity, his messaging, the historical significance of this speech, and the various shushing, swearing, and shouting that occurred. Plus, Axe learns what a Karen is!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 23:28:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8244358.mp3?modified=1675898965&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>I’m Right, You’re Evil (with Mark Mellman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Murphy and Gibbs were joined by Super Pollster Extraordinaire Mark Mellman. The Hacks set the stage for Biden’s State of the Union address: how does this historically impact presidential approval ratings, what are the marching orders Biden will give his base, and how will he define the Republican Party? They also look back at the 2022 midterms, discuss Trump campaigning in South Carolina over the weekend, and discuss the Chicago mayor’s race. Plus Murphy challenges you to a joke-off!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 23:39:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8239656.mp3?modified=1675208425&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>No There There (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Bill Kristol, editor-at-large of The Bulwark, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the ongoing classified documents probe and the impact it could have on 2024, Ron Klain’s departure from the White House, and how secret documents should be handled. Plus, Mike “longtime Chicago voter” Murphy shares his thoughts on the upcoming Chicago mayoral election (along with actual voter David Axelrod).&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8235315.mp3?modified=1674607209&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mud On Biden’s Tuxedo</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by Super Hackeroo Douglas Heye who led comms shops in the House, Senate, and for the RNC. The Hacks dive into the nuances and intricacies of the House Rules Committee, discuss the enigma that is George Santos (is that really his name?), the Biden classified documents saga, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 01:48:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8231665.mp3?modified=1674006610&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>C-SPAN’s Greatest Hits (with Dave Wasserman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks kick off 2023 with esteemed guest Dave Wasserman of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter. Axe, Murphy, and Wasserman discuss the dramatic election for Speaker of the House and what it reveals about internal House dynamics, the discovery of classified documents in Biden’s private office, the Biden administration’s stance on immigration, and upcoming elections around the country to keep an eye on, including the Chicago mayoral race. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8227489.mp3?modified=1673404668&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The First Annual Hacky Awards!</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks convene to host the first annual post-midterm end of year holiday spectacular award show! Join us as we award the biggest winners and losers of 2022, the biggest political story of the year, best and worst campaigns of the year, the biggest missed story of 2022, the biggest story to expect in 2023, and the Hacks give honorable mentions to the rising stars in each party! We hope you have a Hacky New Year!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 01:35:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8218745.mp3?modified=1671586624&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Palace Intrigue (with Doug Heye)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by Hackeroo (and very friendly guy) Doug Heye. Doug taps into his experience as the former communications director for the RNC and deputy chief of staff to Eric Cantor to discuss the Republican in-fighting for the next Speaker of the House. The Hacks also discuss the strategy behind Sinema leaving the Democratic Party, how that shapes upcoming races, and so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 23:59:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8213723.mp3?modified=1670976069&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Run Off Run Up (with Mo Elleithee)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Mo Elleithee, former communications director for the Democratic National Committee and current executive director of the Georgetown Institute of Politics, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss all things Georgia on runoff day — the final ads, Biden and Trump’s influence there, and what the results will mean for both parties. Mo also walks us through the new primary schedules and how that could reshape elections as we know them! Plus so much more!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:50:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8209532.mp3?modified=1670976966&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Dust Has Settled (with Ron Brownstein)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Gibbs and Murphy were joined by a man whose many titles will take up most of our episode description. He is a Senior Editor at The Atlantic, a Senior Political Analyst for CNN, and the author of “Rock Me on the Water: 1974 — The Year Los Angeles Transformed Movies, Music, Television, and Politics”. Now that the dust has settled they look back on the midterms and discuss the upcoming races, if there are still swing states, and the future of both parties. Plus Ron shares his favorite book! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:33:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8204889.mp3?modified=1669764889&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Crow Episode</title><description>&lt;div&gt;It’s the one-week anniversary of the 2022 midterms and to celebrate Gibbs and Murphy dive deep into the results. The Republicans may have underperformed nationally but where did they make state gains and why? Who is on the Democratic bench for 2024 and who will they face on the Republican side? Does anyone read our listener mailbag questions anymore? All of these questions, and more, will be addressed! Tune in.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 01:01:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8197533.mp3?modified=1668560594&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Prepping for the Apocalypse from Story of the Week</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Here’s a preview of a new podcast, Story of the Week. Each week, journalist Joel Stein chooses an article that fascinates him, convinces the writer to tell him about it, and then interrupts a good conversation by talking about himself. Sometimes the story will be the one everyone is talking about, like the New Yorker article on smoking hallucinogenic toads. Other times, it’s a story you might have missed, like the one in the Verge about the rock groupie turned hacker who had huge corporations at her mercy. Stories that stick with you long after you forget whatever headline you just doom-scrolled through. In this preview, Joel is joined by Douglas Rushkoff to talk about his experience speaking to a group of tech billionaires in the middle of the desert. He thought he’d be chatting about the latest in tech advancements, but all these guys wanted to talk about was building doomsday bunkers. Hear the full episode, and more from Story of the Week at &lt;a href="https://podcasts.pushkin.fm/sotw?sid=hacks"&gt;https://podcasts.pushkin.fm/sotw?sid=hacks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8195164.mp3?modified=1668197047&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Whackadoodle Factor (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The midterm special hackathon extravaganza is finally here and we couldn’t think of a better guest to join us than POLITICO’s Politics Bureau Chief and Senior Columnist, Jonathan Martin. The Hacks discuss the results we have from the midterms and breakdown what that means for control of the Senate, House, and eventually The White House!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:59:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8194767.mp3?modified=1668139241&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Only Poll That Matters</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In their final episode before the midterms all three Hacks convene to discuss Obama emerging on the campaign trail, they update us on key races including: Georgia, Nevada, Pennsylvania, and Utah — and they prepare us for the midterms — will it be a ripple or a wave? And don’t forget, your vote matters, VOTE!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:39:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8186395.mp3?modified=1667349656&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Dire, Not Catastrophic (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by a super esteemed Hackeroo, the formidable Amy Walter, publisher and editor-in-chief of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter. Together they put on their beer goggles to look back on past elections for context on today’s polarization; discuss upcoming debates, viral moments, and narrative benders; and talk all things midterms and gut instincts. Plus David’s dog, Mac, gets a shoutout! Woof! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:54:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8181060.mp3?modified=1666745742&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Double Dive (with Jon Ralston &amp; Greg Bluestein)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by two formidable and local Hacks to deep dive into the Nevada and Georgia races. First up is Nevada! Jon Ralston, CEO of the Nevada Independent, joined us to discuss the Cortez Masto v. Laxalt Senate race and walks as through the intricacies of the Nevada ballot. Then we’re joined by Greg Bluestein, author of “Flipped: How Georgia Turned Purple and Broke the Monopoly on Republican Power,” who breaks down the Walker v. Warnock Senate race, discusses the Georgia Governor’s race, and is kind enough to invite Gibbs and Murphy over for Thanksgiving! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 23:49:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8176968.mp3?modified=1666137033&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Great Pageantry of Democracy</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the Hacks were joined by Superstar Hack Extraordinaire Jonathan Martin to discuss Trump’s rally in Arizona, the optics of GOP candidates aligning themselves with the former president, the strategy of participation in midterm debates this cycle, and so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:50:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8173141.mp3?modified=1665535888&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Values Vs. Issues (With Molly Murphy)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;With five weeks to go before the election, it’s Murphy madness as we welcome Molly Murphy, Democratic pollster and strategist, to the show. Axe, Murphy, and the other Murphy discuss the continued impact of the Dobbs decision—among other issues—on voter enthusiasm, new allegations against Herschel Walker, and the races that will determine control of the Senate.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 01:38:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8169314.mp3?modified=1664933995&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Introducing: It Was Said Season 2</title><description>&lt;div&gt;It Was Said, the 2021 Webby Award winner for Best Podcast Series, returns with a new season to look back on some of the most powerful, impactful, and timeless speeches in history. Written and narrated by Pulitzer Prize winner and bestselling author-historian Jon Meacham, this documentary podcast series takes you through another season of ten generation-defining speeches. Meacham, along with top historians, authors and journalists, offers expert insight and analysis into the origins, the orator, and the context of the times each speech was given, and they reflect on why it’s important to never forget them. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It Was Said is a creation and production of Peabody-nominated C13Originals, in association with The HISTORY® Channel.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8166066.mp3?modified=1664468188&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Polls &amp; Pols (with David Hill)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Republican pollster and strategist Dr. David Hill joins Murphy and fellow Auburn fan Gibbs to discuss how this midterm cycle compares to cycles in the past, the likelihood of split ticket voting in Georgia and elsewhere, whether there’s a brewing rivalry between Governors Greg Abbott and Ron DeSantis, and share tips and tricks for being a sophisticated consumer of polls.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 22:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8164942.mp3?modified=1664317104&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Culture Vultures (with Mo Elleithee)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Mo Elleithee, former communications director for the Democratic National Committee and current executive director of the Georgetown Institute of Politics, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Democrats’ attempt to defy gravity this election cycle, Ron DeSantis’ political stunts, and the cultural issues dominant in both parties today. Plus, the Hacks review the races that will determine control of the US Senate and break down Biden’s comments about 2024.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 23:31:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8160999.mp3?modified=1663716771&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Irrational Exuberance? (with Jon Favreau)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Jon Favreau, “podcasting royalty” and former speechwriter for Barack Obama, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Democratic enthusiasm around the country, the critical role suburban voters will play in this year’s midterm elections, key Senate races to watch, and insights from focus groups on the new season of Jon’s podcast, The Wilderness.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:13:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8157168.mp3?modified=1663114487&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Midterm Sprint</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Murphy convene the day after Labor Day to kick off the official sprint to the midterms. They discuss Biden’s decision to go after MAGA Republicans, the wisdom of both Biden and Trump inserting themselves in the middle of the campaign conversation, how the Dobbs decision may impact turnout in November, and Murphy takes us on trip across the pond for an update on UK politics. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 22:57:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8153038.mp3?modified=1662505130&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bully Boy Tactics (with Mark Leibovich)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Atlantic’s Mark Leibovich joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Biden’s messaging on the campaign trail ahead of the midterms, Ron DeSantis’ political future, the primaries in Florida and New York, and insights from Mark’s book, &lt;em&gt;Thank You for Your Servitude: Donald Trump’s Washington and the Price of Submission&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:01:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8144630.mp3?modified=1661299360&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Ferret Vs. The Boa Constrictor (with Maggie Haberman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;New York Times senior political reporter Maggie Haberman joins Axe and Murphy to discuss how the FBI’s search of Mar-a-Lago impacts Trump’s political capital, whether the Department of Justice adequately understood the current political environment, Trump’s relationship with Kevin McCarthy, and what to expect from today’s primaries in Wyoming and Alaska. Plus, Maggie previews her forthcoming book, &lt;em&gt;Confidence Man: The Making of Donald Trump and the Breaking of America&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 23:08:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8140544.mp3?modified=1660691383&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Where to Mar-a-LaGO From Here? (with Whit Ayres)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Republican pollster and strategist Whit Ayres joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss the FBI search of Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago home, Biden and the Democrats’ string of legislative victories and whether it will translate to success in the midterms, the status of key Senate races around the country, and the polling trends to watch this fall.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 01:54:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8136247.mp3?modified=1660096535&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Vengeance Tour</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks are back with plenty of snacks to break down the results of an illuminating primary night. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy discuss the surprising voter turnout in Kansas, the fate of pro-impeachment Republicans around the country, the growing slate of election deniers in key states, President Biden’s winning streak, and Speaker Pelosi’s trip to Taiwan.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:25:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8132691.mp3?modified=1659572778&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Elephant in the Room (with Lis Smith)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Democratic strategist Lis Smith, author of Any Given Tuesday: A Political Love Story, joins Axe and Murphy to talk about the season finale of the January 6th hearings, Trump and Pence’s dueling speeches, the shifting size of the red wave in the midterms, and whether Biden finally has some bumper sticker wins under his belt. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 23:57:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8127868.mp3?modified=1658879901&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Build Back Biden (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, formidable Hack and CNN contributor Paul Begala joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss the unraveling of Build Back Better, the strategy of the 1/6 committee in advance of their highly anticipated hearing on Thursday, Trump’s donor courting tour, and - in between Murphy swooning over big oil - we venture across the pond* to discuss UK politics. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
*No horrible British accents were included in this recording of Hacks on Tap.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 22:44:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8123880.mp3?modified=1658270775&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>One More Item…</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks are back to discuss whether the Department of Justice could indict Donald Trump, recent polling from The New York Times and what it portends for both Biden and Trump’s political future, how Biden should respond to questions about 2024, and the Senate race in Georgia. Plus, Murphy gets an opportunity to gloat and use the word “chortle,” a Hacks on Tap first.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8120371.mp3?modified=1657758819&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Precedent-Shattering</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks respond to a slightly delayed bat signal in this special edition of Hacks on Tap to break down the shocking testimony during the Jan. 6th hearings, whether the latest revelations impact Trump’s political future, the ramifications for the midterms, and whether Biden has a newfound opportunity to take charge on domestic issues.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 18:53:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8112497.mp3?modified=1656615285&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Prosecuting the Case (with Sarah Longwell)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Sarah Longwell, publisher of The Bulwark and host of The Focus Group podcast, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss how Trump voters are reacting to the January 6th hearings, the Supreme Court’s decision to overturn Roe vs. Wade and whether it gives Democrats an opportunity to go on offense in the midterms, Mitch McConnell’s approach to the bipartisan gun control bill, Elise Stefanik’s hard turn to towards Trumpism, and more.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 02:15:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8111384.mp3?modified=1656469028&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Atomic Clock of Corruption (with Amanda Carpenter)</title><description>Amanda Carpenter, political columnist for The Bulwark, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Trump’s political future in light of the Jan. 6 committee’s findings, the shocking number of election deniers on the ballot across the country, the merits of a gas tax holiday, Biden’s upcoming trip to Saudi Arabia, and the LA mayor’s race.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8106879.mp3?modified=1655854316&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Barr Tab (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John Heilemann, host of the Hell &amp;amp; High Water podcast and executive editor of The Recount, is back with Axe and Murphy to discuss the revelations from the January 6th hearings, President Biden’s limited toolkit on inflation and what it means for the midterms, whispers of Biden’s political future, the bipartisan gun bill, and the races to watch in South Carolina.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:04:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8102561.mp3?modified=1655251579&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Introducing The Powers That Be: Daily</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Join Emmy Award-winning journalist Peter Hamby, along with the team of expert journalists at Puck, as they let you in on the real conversations insiders are having across the four corners of power in America: Wall Street, Washington, Silicon Valley and Hollywood. Puck's contributors bring you smart conversation around the inside stories happening in these worlds. Presented in partnership with Cadence13 Studios, this podcast releases new episodes daily, Monday-Friday.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8100094.mp3?modified=1654882507&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>California Scheming (with Dave Wasserman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Dave Wasserman, US House editor of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the plethora of primaries happening around the country, what the results from recent races tell us about the national political environment, whether any voters will be swayed by the January 6th committee hearings, and how the politics of gun control will play out in suburban areas this fall.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8097129.mp3?modified=1654647758&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Swimming Against the Current (with Doug Sosnik)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Doug Sosnik, former senior advisor to President Bill Clinton, joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss the headwinds Democrats face in the midterms and the importance of narrative storytelling in politics. Plus, the Hacks take a close look at the Senate race in Pennsylvania and dive into the jumbo mailbag.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 02:02:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8093544.mp3?modified=1654049075&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>“What Are We Doing?”</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks convene for what was supposed to be an election night recap but instead was an all too familiar discussion on gun violence in America. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy talk about the latest school shooting in Texas, the politics of gun control, and the results of Tuesday night’s primary races.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 22:32:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8090037.mp3?modified=1653518036&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The MAGA Midterms?</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Murphy break down the results from the primary races in a number of key states in this special edition of Hacks on Tap. They discuss the highly-anticipated Republican Senate race in Pennsylvania, the fate of Congressman Madison Cawthorn and other candidates backed by Trump, how progressive Democratic candidates fared across the country, and ultimately the fact that Trumpism is alive and well.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:20:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8086161.mp3?modified=1652905327&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Personality Politics (with Jonathan Martin &amp; Alex Burns)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;We’ve reached maximum Hacks capacity this week with not one but two guest Hacks, Jonathan Martin and Alex Burns of The New York Times. They join Axe and Murphy to discuss the MAGA-fication of Republican primary races, the politics of Roe v. Wade, and Martin and Burns’ new book, This Will Not Pass: Trump, Biden, and the Battle for America’s Future.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 01:42:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8081434.mp3?modified=1652233439&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>SCOTUS Leaks and Ohio Speaks</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy followed the bat signal and convened for a special edition of Hacks on Tap. They discuss the results of the Ohio primary election, what JD Vance’s (or is it JP?) victory says about Trump and Trumpism, the bombshell leak out of the Supreme Court, and how the politics of Roe v. Wade will influence voter turnout in the midterms. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 03:31:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8078204.mp3?modified=1651721586&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mouse Trap: DeSantis vs. Disney (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Mark McKinnon, executive producer and co-host of The Circus, joins Axe and Gibbs to talk about Ron DeSantis’ war with Mickey Mouse, leaked audio of Kevin McCarthy after January 6th, why the midterms will exacerbate polarization in Congress, and what it takes to craft a strong campaign slogan.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 23:53:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8073282.mp3?modified=1651017324&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Ping Pong Politics (with Whit Ayres)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Whit Ayres, Republican pollster and strategist, joins Gibbs and Murphy to talk about the power of Trump’s endorsement in primary races, the states to watch this fall, and how our political system has become unstable. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 02:16:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8069552.mp3?modified=1650421065&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Some Other Dude Did It (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Paul Begala, CNN contributor and former counselor to President Bill Clinton, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss rising consumer prices, the “some other dude did it” defense, Biden’s budding immigration issue, and Trump’s endorsement of Dr. Oz in Pennsylvania. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8065986.mp3?modified=1649809006&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Introducing Reflections of History with Jon Meacham</title><description>&lt;div&gt;C13 Originals and Pulitzer Prize winner and best-selling author Jon Meacham, co-creators of the 2021 Webby Award-winning Best Podcast Series It Was Said and the acclaimed podcast Hope, Through History, join together again for a brand-new series that will guide listeners through critical moments in our history. Every Monday through Friday, Meacham travels back to impactful events that occurred on that date in history—the birth of a visionary filmmaker, the debut of an iconic athlete, the discovery of a lifesaving cure, a triumphant legal victory. You’ll learn how that event shaped politics, art, culture, sports and science, and why it’s still relevant today. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8063915.mp3?modified=1649447163&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Gas &amp; Groceries (with Steve Israel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Former Congressman and chair of the DCCC Steve Israel joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss the domestic policy challenges that stem from the war in Ukraine, Democrats’ strategy for the midterms, the special election in Alaska, and what will move swing voters in November.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8061382.mp3?modified=1649200625&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Walkback of the Walkback</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Axe and Gibbs were joined by the inimitable New York Times reporter and CNN analyst Maggie Haberman to discuss Biden’s trip to Poland, the January 6th committee, Trump on the campaign trail, and so much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 23:32:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8056622.mp3?modified=1648596863&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Chronicles of the Culture Wars (with Ron Brownstein)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Journalist and CNN senior political analyst Ron Brownstein joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Ketanji Brown Jackson’s Supreme Court confirmation hearings, how the culture wars may shape upcoming elections, the changing demographics in the country, and the races that will decide control of the Senate.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 22:18:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8052638.mp3?modified=1647987641&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bad For Business (with Stephanie Cutter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Democratic strategist and communications guru Stephanie Cutter joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the Biden administration’s response to the ongoing crisis in Ukraine, the importance of message discipline for both parties as we approach the midterms, the latest polling numbers, and Biden’s nominee for the Supreme Court. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 23:08:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8047986.mp3?modified=1647385817&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Margin of Error (with Mark Mellman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Pollster Mark Mellman joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss the domestic political implications of Biden’s decision to ban Russian energy imports, how Democrats should move forward with their agenda ahead of the midterm elections, and the growing influence of Latino voters in the US.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:42:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8044132.mp3?modified=1646786653&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>State of the State of the Union</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The Hacks convene for a special late-night recap of President Biden’s first State of the Union address. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy discuss Biden’s rebuke of Putin, the moments of rare bipartisan unity, the speech’s messaging misses and successes, and the country’s esteemed designated survivor.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 08:51:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8040383.mp3?modified=1646211191&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The State of the Union Is… (with Jon Favreau)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Jon Favreau, co-host of Pod Save America, host of Offline, and former speechwriter for Barack Obama, joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss Biden’s condemnation of Putin’s aggression toward Ukraine, the political implications of US sanctions against Russia, what Biden needs to accomplish in his upcoming State of the Union speech, and whether Trump’s legal troubles will impact his political future.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:24:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8036474.mp3?modified=1645590362&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The RINO Rebellion? (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Amy Walter, publisher and editor-in-chief of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the latest in the Trump vs. McConnell saga, the political influence of parents, and Biden’s upcoming State of the Union speech.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8032178.mp3?modified=1644972174&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Legitimate Political Discourse</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Not one but two guest Hacks join Axe this week while Murphy and Gibbs are away on assignment. John Heilemann, Executive Editor of The Recount, and Amanda Carpenter, political columnist for The Bulwark, chat with Axe about Mike Pence’s attempt to pivot away from Trump, the RNC’s censure of Adam Kinzinger and Liz Cheney, whether Democrats should invoke Trump in the midterm elections, the latest chapter of Covid politics, and Biden’s Supreme Court nomination process.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8028064.mp3?modified=1644372216&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Eruption of Mt. Orange</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, the Hacks assemble to mark episode number 150. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy discuss the strength of Trump’s grip on the GOP, the latest in the standoff with Russia, the politics of the Supreme Court, and why at the end of the day, political messaging rules all.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 02:54:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8023380.mp3?modified=1643770547&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Reset Report Card (with Jennifer Palmieri)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Jennifer Palmieri, co-host of Showtime’s The Circus and former White House communications director, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss Biden’s hot mic moment, escalating tensions with Russia over Ukraine, how the Biden administration should communicate the story of America’s resilience, and Newt Gingrich’s gift to Democrats.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8019147.mp3?modified=1643156147&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Almighty vs The Alternative (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;As the anniversary of President Biden’s inauguration approaches, the Hacks called in Jonathan Martin, a national political correspondent for The New York Times, to reflect on Biden’s first year in office. They discuss whether Biden needs a reset, the fate of some of the administration’s key legislation, the messaging and campaign strategies for both parties in the midterms, and if we’re witnessing the early signs of a Donald Trump vs Ron DeSantis showdown.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 02:02:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8015227.mp3?modified=1642557848&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Joltin’ Joe Comes Out Swinging (with Addisu Demissie)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Democratic political strategist Addisu Demissie joins Axe and Murphy to discuss President Biden’s speech on the anniversary of the January 6th attack on the Capitol, his condemnation of Trump, the voting rights fight, and the fate of the filibuster in the Senate. The Hacks also posit their essay contest vs. multiple choice election theory and examine the 2022 Senate map. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 23:52:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8011137.mp3?modified=1641945250&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Madman Behind The Curtain</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Mark McKinnon, the Stetson-wearing executive producer and co-host of Showtime’s the Circus, joins Gibbs and Murphy to help the Hacks kick off 2022. With the one-year anniversary of January 6th looming, the Hacks discuss the House select committee’s investigation into the attack on the Capitol, Trump’s legal troubles, and what Biden can learn from Hollywood.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 01:57:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8007514.mp3?modified=1641347966&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacky Holidays, Mailbag Edition!</title><description>&lt;div&gt;To mark the end of 2021, Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy convene for a special holiday mailbag edition of Hacks on Tap. The Hacks discuss Manchin’s Build Back Better bombshell before taking questions from our esteemed listeners. Plus, Murphy’s year is made when a very special guest makes a surprise appearance.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8001848.mp3?modified=1640146980&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>GOPuppets (with Steve Bullock)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Former Montana Governor Steve Bullock joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the warning signs he sees for Democrats in rural America, the messaging challenges around Biden’s Build Back Better bill, the latest revelations from the January 6th committee, and speculation about the 2024 presidential race.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 02:40:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7997144.mp3?modified=1639536145&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>20/24 Vision (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Bill Kristol, editor-at-large of The Bulwark and director of Defending Democracy Together, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss some of the must-watch races in 2022, Trump’s continued efforts to subvert our democracy, and Kristol provides his “lit” 2024 Democratic ticket prediction.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:30:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7992978.mp3?modified=1638923541&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Kitten Swipes and Variant Fights (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John Heilemann, executive editor of The Recount and host of the Hell &amp;amp; High Water podcast, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the political ramifications of the new coronavirus variant, whether the Biden administration should wade into the culture wars, and the shocking normalization of political violence in this country. Plus, Murphy introduces us to the one and only Uncle Walt.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:42:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7988847.mp3?modified=1638319430&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Inflation Nation (with Tony Fabrizio)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Veteran Republican pollster and strategist Tony Fabrizio joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the long-awaited signing of the bipartisan infrastructure bill into law, whether the legislation will have a measurable impact on upcoming elections, the political implications for rising prices, and this week’s “WTF” moment. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:40:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7981417.mp3?modified=1637109713&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Process Over Substance (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Amy Walter, publisher and editor-in-chief of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the disconnect between the positive economic indicators and Americans’ pessimism about the state of the country, the passage of the infrastructure bill and the messaging opportunities and challenges it presents for the Biden administration, and the Hacks experience their own supply chain issues live on air.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7976869.mp3?modified=1636509712&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Dems In Disarray?</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy assemble to discuss Election Day 2021, including the rough night for Democrats, the impact of national politics on local races, the reset Democrats—and Biden—need in order to avoid huge losses in the midterms, and whether Glenn Youngkin has successfully cracked the code when it comes to GOP success in the Trump era. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7973080.mp3?modified=1635977380&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Off To The Races (with Dave Wasserman)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Dave Wasserman, US House editor of the Cook Political Report with Amy Walter, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the final stretch of the Virginia governor’s race, the impact of Democrats’ actions—or lack thereof—in Congress on the upcoming election, and the latest redistricting developments and projections for the midterms. Plus, Wasserman reveals how he came up with his iconic phrase, “I’ve seen enough.”&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 01:12:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7967918.mp3?modified=1635297269&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>All Roads Go Through Virginia</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week the hacks look into their crystal ball with former Virginia Congressman Tom Davis to discuss Virginia’s upcoming gubernatorial election. Then, they time travel to figure out how Biden can make big moves to pass his infrastructure bill and how the 2022 midterms could effect leadership positions in both the Democratic and Republican Party. Plus, Murphy taps into his artistic side when he answers a listener question from the mailbag!&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 22:12:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7963729.mp3?modified=1634681624&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Shot Clock Ticks</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week, Steve Israel, former Congressman and future bookshop owner, joined Axe and Murphy to talk about Trump’s endorsement of Chuck Grassley, Trump’s power over the GOP and how Dems can use it to fuel turnout in 2022, the Virginia Governor’s race, never-ending negotiations on the hill, and much more! &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 23:47:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7959277.mp3?modified=1634082590&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Here’s The Deal?</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy are together again (and full of puns) to discuss Biden hitting the road to tout his “Build Back Better” plan, the debt ceiling debacle, Trump’s upcoming trip to Iowa, and the latest in Virginia’s gubernatorial race. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 23:36:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7955174.mp3?modified=1633477079&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Where the Rubber Meets the Road (with John Anzalone)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John Anzalone, a longtime Democratic pollster who polls for President Biden, joins Gibbs and Murphy to talk about this “eventful” week in Washington. The Hacks discuss Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s latest plan for the infrastructure bill and the Democrats’ reconciliation bill, how the events of this week might impact messaging for the 2022 midterm elections, and President Biden’s approval rating.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 23:32:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7950581.mp3?modified=1632872019&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A High-Wire Act (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Jonathan Martin, a national political correspondent for The New York Times, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the rift between progressive and moderate Democrats over the size and scope of their economic agenda, the latest example of Trump’s grip on the Republican Party, and whether foreign policy matters to voters. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 23:49:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7946373.mp3?modified=1632268248&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A New Day For Newsom (with Dana Bash)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Dana Bash, CNN’s chief political correspondent, co-anchor of State of the Union, and host of the new podcast Total Recall: California’s Political Circus, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the results of the California recall election and the key takeaways for Democrats’ messaging as we head into the midterms. The Hacks also cover the latest on the Democrats’ social spending package and ponder whether Independents are truly independent.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 01:55:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7943172.mp3?modified=1631758176&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Can the Golden State Stay Blue? (with Peter Hamby)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Peter Hamby, host of Snapchat’s Good Luck America and founding partner of and contributor to Puck, joins Gibbs and Murphy for a deep dive into the upcoming recall election in California, including how the effort to remove Governor Gavin Newsom from office came to be and their predictions about whether he survives. Plus, the Hacks discuss Texas’ new abortion ban and its impact on the 2022 midterm elections.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:27:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7937568.mp3?modified=1631057384&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Short vs. Long Term (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Axe and Gibbs are joined by Bill Kristol, editor-at-large of The Bulwark, to discuss the public perception and political ramifications of the withdrawal from Afghanistan, the resurgence of COVID and its implications for Biden’s approval rating and beyond, and the needle Nancy Pelosi must thread in order to advance Biden’s agenda. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 23:50:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7929758.mp3?modified=1629849146&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Collapse of Afghanistan</title><description>&lt;div&gt;It’s all Hacks on deck this week as Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy convene to discuss the Taliban’s takeover of Afghanistan, the scenes of panic and chaos in Kabul, Biden’s address to the nation, and the political implications of it all. Plus, the Hacks unpack the latest in the Democrats’ efforts to pass Biden’s economic agenda and the most recent developments in the California recall election.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:04:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7925816.mp3?modified=1629245186&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pugnacious Pols &amp; Bipartisan Bills (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Paul Begala, CNN contributor and former counselor to President Clinton, joins Axe and Murphy to help make sense of not one but two breaking news alerts in the span of one hour. The Hacks discuss the most recent efforts by some members of the GOP to further politicize the pandemic, the resignation of New York Governor Andrew Cuomo, the Senate’s passage of the bipartisan infrastructure bill, and where the legislation goes from here.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 01:19:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7922083.mp3?modified=1628644876&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mixed Messages (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Private first class hackaroo Mark McKinnon, executive producer and co-host of Showtime’s The Circus, joins Axe and Gibbs to talk about the CDC’s messaging mishaps, the New York Attorney General’s finding that Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed state employees, and how much political currency bipartisanship actually wields. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 01:07:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7917849.mp3?modified=1628039351&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>U.S. House of Horrors (with Jackie Calmes)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Jackie Calmes, national columnist for the Los Angeles Times and author of Dissent: The Radicalization of the Republican Party and Its Capture of the Court, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the powerful testimony delivered during the opening hearing on the insurrection, the latest bumps in the road for infrastructure negotiations, the impact of the Delta variant on Biden's agenda, and the "Shakespearean" tales playing out around the country.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:35:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7912687.mp3?modified=1627432623&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Baseball Bats and Ghirardelli (with Steve Israel)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week Gibbs and Murphy were joined by former Congressman Steve Israel who graciously shared his expertise as a former Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee Chair to discuss redistricting, campaign fundraising, and the upcoming 2022 midterms. They also discussed infrastructure negotiations and the (both physical and metaphorical) tools Nancy Pelosi uses to negotiate, Murphy explains his WWII analogy, and more! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:26:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7908844.mp3?modified=1626827279&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Texas Hold ‘Em (with Al Franken)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Former Minnesota Senator Al Franken joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the latest lunacy to come out of CPAC, the escalating fight over voting rights and the possibility of a filibuster carve-out, and whether the largest price spike since 2008 will impact negotiations in Congress.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 01:13:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7904666.mp3?modified=1626225334&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Tale of Two Tracks (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Bill Kristol, editor-at-large of The Bulwark and director of Defending Democracy Together, joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss efforts to increase vaccination rates amid heightened concerns about the Delta variant, the two-track infrastructure legislation, the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead for Vice President Kamala Harris, and the politics of US withdrawal from Afghanistan.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 23:19:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7899777.mp3?modified=1625613750&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Rocky Road (with Stephanie Cutter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Democratic political strategist and communications expert Stephanie Cutter joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the efforts to save the bipartisan infrastructure deal after Biden’s botched rollout, the early jockeying among ’24 GOP presidential hopefuls to capture the Trump base, and whether Vice President Kamala Harris has been set up for success. Plus, the Hacks discuss the triumph that was the reimagined Democratic National Convention and inauguration celebration, both of which are eligible for Emmy Awards.  &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 23:34:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7895939.mp3?modified=1625009795&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Tyranny of the Minority (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Amy Walter, national editor of the Cook Political Report and a PBS NewsHour contributor, joins Axe and Gibbs to talk about the “political theater” surrounding the voting rights bill, the likelihood that Democrats stay united on infrastructure spending, and how rising crime in New York City has shaped the focus of the city’s mayoral primary. &lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 22:29:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7891690.mp3?modified=1624401096&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Biden Takes the World Stage (with Howard Wolfson)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Howard Wolfson, Democratic political strategist and former Deputy Mayor of New York City, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Joe Biden’s first foreign trip as president, why this is a pivotal moment for democracy, and the challenges that remain for a bipartisan infrastructure bill. Plus, the Hacks take a deep dive into New York City’s mayoral race and explore the ways in which the primary is a microcosm of the debate over messaging in the Democratic Party.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 22:47:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7887443.mp3?modified=1623797416&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Infra-STUCK-ure (with Charlie Sykes)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Charlie Sykes, Editor at Large of The Bulwark, host of the Bulwark Podcast, and author of “How the Right Lost Its Mind” joined Gibbs and an optimistic Murphy to discuss the overtime infrastructure talks, Senator Manchin and good faith negotiations, Trump’s return to the campaign trail, and what this all means for the 2022 midterms.&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:19:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7883323.mp3?modified=1623199367&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Building Bridges (with Jonathan Martin)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Martin, a national political correspondent for The New York Times, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the make or break moment for infrastructure talks, whether a bill to restrict voting in Texas will reinvigorate the voting rights debate in the Senate, and why 2021 might be the best of times and the worst of times for progressives. Plus, the Hacks discussion Jonathan’s reporting on how races in New Mexico and Arkansas are test cases for both parties ahead of the midterms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 21:33:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7878678.mp3?modified=1622584042&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Infrastructure Week? (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the latest twists and turns in the negotiations over infrastructure spending and Biden’s agenda more broadly, the continued GOP infighting, and whether foreign policy—and the recent conflict between Israel and Hamas—will be a priority for voters in the 2022 midterm elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:47:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7874014.mp3?modified=1621987392&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Inconvenient Truths (with Barbara Comstock)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Republican Congresswoman Barbara Comstock joins Axe and Murphy to discuss what lies ahead for the GOP after Rep. Liz Cheney’s removal from House leadership, the likelihood that a commission to investigate the Jan. 6 Capitol attack will be established, the politics of unmasking, and how the Supreme Court’s decision to hear an abortion case could impact the midterm elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:19:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7869285.mp3?modified=1621384780&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Weather Vanes &amp; Freedom Fights (with Mark Mellman)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Democratic pollster and strategist Mark Mellman joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss the impending removal of Rep. Liz Cheney from House Republican leadership, what her likely departure says about internal GOP dynamics, the latest wave of controversial voting laws, and Biden’s proposed tax increase and what it portends for the midterms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 23:21:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7863343.mp3?modified=1620776122&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Davos of Bipartisanship (with Karl Rove)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Karl Rove, former deputy chief of staff to President George W. Bush and current Fox News contributor and Wall Street Journal columnist, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the latest GOP infighting and Trump’s continued influence on the party, how redistricting will impact the 2022 midterms and beyond, and whether a bipartisan agreement on anything from infrastructure to immigration can be reached in Congress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 01:10:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7858886.mp3?modified=1620178363&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Welcome to Fate of Fact</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a new audio documentary, Fate of Fact, a presentation of Shining City Audio, a C13Originals and Jon Meacham studio. Throughout the course of five episodes in season one, Pulitzer-Prize winning and best-selling historian, Jon Meacham and esteemed guests, will explore the question of how fear conquered truth, the history and origins of the strong grip misinformation and disinformation have on our politics , and how we got here today. Meacham will trace the roots of America’s prevailing culture of polarization, with an emphasis on why the right has chosen to break with a governing consensus that, however imperfect, was once embodied by the figurative conversation between Franklin Roosevelt and Ronald Reagan. Fate of Fact offers a historically grounded perspective on the forces that led to the presidency of Donald Trump and the insurrection of January 6—an attack on the Capitol and on democracy as grave as any American moment since the Civil War. ​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7857462.mp3?modified=1620025759&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>America on the Move</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs convene for a special late-night edition of Hacks on Tap after Biden’s first address to Congress. The Hacks discuss Biden’s ambitious agenda as he marks 100 days in office, Sen. Tim Scott’s rebuttal, the forthcoming “battle of definition,” and whether the president’s case for democracy will prevail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 08:01:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856206.mp3?modified=1619789021&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Yoda and the Lessons of Power (with Susan Page)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;USA TODAY Washington Bureau Chief Susan Page joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Walter Mondale’s legacy, the ongoing negotiations around Biden’s infrastructure proposal, the politics of gun control, and their assessment of Biden’s first 100 days. Plus, the Hacks talk about Susan’s new biography of Speaker Nancy Pelosi, Madam Speaker: Nancy Pelosi and the Lessons of Power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856207.mp3?modified=1619788974&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Ants Go Marching (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gibbs and Murphy are joined this week by Mark McKinnon, executive producer and co-host of Showtime’s The Circus. The Hacks discuss the messaging opportunities and challenges ahead for both parties when it comes to Biden’s infrastructure plan, the tragic police shooting in Minnesota, and the GOP pilgrimage to Mar-a-Lago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856208.mp3?modified=1619789038&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Infrastructuring (with Will Hurd)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Texas Congressman Will Hurd joins Axe and Gibbs this week to discuss the battle over the shape and size of Biden’s infrastructure bill, Major League Baseball’s decision to pull the All-Star Game out of Atlanta in response to Georgia’s new controversial voting law, and the political influence of corporate America.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 01:14:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856209.mp3?modified=1619789032&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Politics of the Possible (with Ron Brownstein)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;wJournalist and CNN senior political analyst Ron Brownstein joins Axe and Murphy to discuss how the politicization of the pandemic will impact elections in ’22 and ’24, the messaging opportunities and challenges ahead for Biden around his economic plan, and the ongoing fight over voting rights. Plus, the Hacks dive into Brownstein’s new book Rock Me on the Water: 1974 — The Year Los Angeles Transformed Movies, Music, Television, and Politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 23:56:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856210.mp3?modified=1619789005&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Godzilla &amp; The GOP (with Tony Fabrizio)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Veteran Republican pollster and strategist Tony Fabrizio, who served as Trump’s chief pollster in ’16 and ’20, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss his analysis of the five “tribes” that make up the current Republican Party and what it says about the power Trump holds over the GOP. Plus, in the wake of the second mass shooting in less than a week, the Hacks discuss the politics of gun control and whether or not Congress will advance any new legislation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:54:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856211.mp3?modified=1619789021&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Shots In Arms &amp; Checks In Pockets (with Claire McCaskill)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Missouri Senator and current NBC &amp;amp; MSNBC analyst Claire McCaskill joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss how President Biden’s recovery plan will impact the 2022 midterm elections, the politics of the southern border and immigration reform, the great press conference scandal of 2021, and how we can begin to heal some of our political divides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856212.mp3?modified=1619789065&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Voting Rights and Filibuster Fights (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the passage of the COVID relief bill in the Senate, the ongoing debate about filibuster reform, and the fight around voting rights. Plus, the Hacks dive into the latest GOP infighting and offer advice about how to effectively communicate policy wins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 02:21:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856213.mp3?modified=1619789007&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>When CPACs Attack (with Scott Jennings)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by Scott Jennings, a GOP strategist, conservative columnist, and CNN commentator. In the wake of Trump’s first public appearance since leaving office, the Hacks discuss the divisions in the Republican Party, the challenges of governing vs campaigning, and the allegations against Governor Andrew Cuomo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 01:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856214.mp3?modified=1619789033&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Blanchin’ From Manchin (with Brad Woodhouse)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Brad Woodhouse, executive director of Protect Our Care and senior advisor to the DNC, joins Gibbs and Murphy to discuss Ted Cruz’s jaunt to Cancun, the politics surrounding the nomination of Neera Tanden to lead the Office of Management and Budget, and how much air time – if any – Trump’s upcoming speech at the Conservative Political Action Conference should receive. Plus, the Hacks pick Brad’s brain about what to expect in the 2022 midterms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:32:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856215.mp3?modified=1619789056&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Impeachment: The Sequel (with Bill Kristol)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Bill Kristol, editor-at-large of The Bulwark, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the historic second impeachment trial of former President Trump and what the Senate’s acquittal means for the future of the GOP. They also analyze some of the early jockeying for the top of the Republican ticket in 2024 and the latest on Biden’s stimulus negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 20:59:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856216.mp3?modified=1619789057&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Introducing The Daily Punch</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Every weekday morning, The Daily Punch brings you inside Capitol Hill, the White House and Washington for an unfiltered look at the key players and stakes of all major issues of the day. People. Power. Politics. Hosted by Punchbowl News founders, journalists, and best-selling authors Anna Palmer and Jake Sherman. Powered by Punchbowl News. Produced by Cadence13. ​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856217.mp3?modified=1619788911&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Greene Achers (with Amanda Carpenter)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined by Amanda Carpenter, a CNN contributor and political columnist for the Bulwark. With the second impeachment trial of former President Trump looming large, the Hacks discuss Trump’s continued grip on the GOP, the dynamics at play within the Republican Party, and the appetite for bipartisanship in Congress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856218.mp3?modified=1619789032&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Unity, Not Unanimity (with Heidi Heitkamp)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former North Dakota Senator Heidi Heitkamp, host of The Hot Dish podcast and co-founder and chair of the One Country Project, joins Axe and Gibbs to discuss the politics and strategy behind the COVID relief package negotiations, the intraparty tension over conspiracy theorists in the Republican party, and what Democrats must do to win back voters in red districts.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 02:37:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856219.mp3?modified=1619789048&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>50+1 Fun</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For the 100th episode of Hacks on Tap, Gibbs and Murphy discuss the political dynamics surrounding Biden’s proposed economic plan, the inner workings of a narrowly divided Senate, and the upcoming impeachment trial of Donald Trump and what it portends for the midterm elections and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856220.mp3?modified=1619789057&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>President Joe Biden</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A few hours after Joe Biden became the 46th President of the United States, Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs convened to recap the historic day. The Hacks reflect on President Biden’s inaugural address, bask in the return to normalcy, and discuss the challenges that lie ahead for our new commander-in-chief. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856221.mp3?modified=1619789080&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pardon Me? (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel joins Axe and Murphy for the final Hacks of the Trump presidency. With unprecedented security measures in place in the nation’s capital, the Hacks discuss the message Joe Biden should convey in his inaugural address, how he should approach his first 100 days in office, the timing of the pending impeachment trial, and Trump’s last second pardon spree. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 03:24:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856222.mp3?modified=1619789156&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>2020: Extra Innings (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy sit down with the one and only John Heilemann to try to make sense of this moment. The Hacks discuss some of the dynamics that contributed to the insurrection, the politics of a second impeachment trial, and Trump’s unwillingness to accept any responsibility for the mob he helped incite. But, it’s not all doom and gloom: The Hacks also discuss the rounding out of Biden’s cabinet, including the one and only Gov. Gina Raimondo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:51:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856223.mp3?modified=1619789170&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Republic, If You Can Keep It</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy sit down at the end of a sad and surreal day in American history. As Congress reconvened to finish certifying President-elect Biden’s victory, the Hacks discuss the insurrection by an angry mob at the US Capitol, the results of the Georgia Senate runoff election, and the politics of this extraordinary moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 06:56:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856224.mp3?modified=1619789168&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacky Holidays!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With the Electoral College handing Biden what felt like his 17th win, Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs convene for the last time this year to bid adieu to 2020. The Hacks discuss the future of Trumpism, Murphy shares his optimistic outlook for American democracy, and Axe and Gibbs squabble over the outcome of stimulus negotiations. So grab a beer and enjoy some holiday Hacks cheer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856225.mp3?modified=1619789215&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Most Gracious Loser (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Gibbs are joined by superhack John Heilemann, now the host of his own podcast “Hell &amp;amp; High Water.” The Hacks discuss the ongoing attempt by Trump to subvert our democracy, take a deep dive into some of the challenges facing the Democratic party in the near term, and talk about the politics of the stimulus negotiations. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856226.mp3?modified=1619789192&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Kook D'Etat (with Jennifer Palmieri)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Palmieri, former White House communications director and host of the podcast “Just Something About Her,” joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Trump’s latest tantrum about election fraud, Biden’s announcement of his communications team and other top administration picks, and how the Republicans must now reap what they sow when it comes to turnout in Georgia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 02:38:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856227.mp3?modified=1619789186&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bonjour, Biden Boom</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs gather to give thanks for a start to the formal transition process and for a slew of qualified cabinet picks by President-elect Biden. They also discuss the looming Georgia runoff election, what a sharper message might look like for both parties, and Murphy finally issues a much-anticipated apology to the French army.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 04:19:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856228.mp3?modified=1619789237&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>My Cousin Rudy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Murphy and Gibbs are joined by President-elect Joe Biden's pollster John Anzalone to talk about what the Hell is going on right now (it's all good, don't worry!), review the decisions the Biden campaign made and go over why they won, dive into Georgia and discuss the state of political polling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 07:27:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856229.mp3?modified=1619789199&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A White House Held Hostage (with Dave Wasserman)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by Dave Wasserman of the Cook Political Report. It’s been two weeks since Election Day and the Hacks continue their postmortem with a deep dive into what happened in congressional districts across the country. They also look ahead to the Georgia special election and discuss what the 2020 race tells us about the future of both parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 01:48:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856230.mp3?modified=1619789267&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump Outrage Fatigue</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With the election in the rear view mirror (and yes, despite what the president says, it is over!) Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs discuss Trump’s ongoing attempts to undermine the institutions of our democracy, speculate about what Trump might do next, and break down the latest Democratic intraparty squabbles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:26:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856231.mp3?modified=1619789215&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>President-Elect Joe Biden</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After election night turned into election week, it’s finally official: Joe Biden is the next President of the United States. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy discuss the results of this unprecedented campaign and the challenges and opportunities ahead for President-Elect Biden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856232.mp3?modified=1619789257&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Election Day Survival Guide</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Well Hackaroos, we’ve arrived. Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs sit down for the last time before Election Day to discuss the final moments of the campaign, what to expect on November 3rd, and when we might have an answer on who will be the next President of the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856233.mp3?modified=1619789293&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>We're Rounding The Corner... To Election Day (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Gibbs are joined by private first class Hackeroo and The Circus' Mark McKinnon to talk about whether Texas will turn blue, what Trump's possible electoral path could be to winning, and the timing of how Election Night's results will roll in next Tuesday. Listen until the end to hear McKinnon's "wild ass forecast" for the GOP 2024 standard bearer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 02:39:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856234.mp3?modified=1619789286&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>T-Minus One Week (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel is back to help Axe and Murphy begin the one week countdown to Election Day. With COVID dominating the airwaves, the Hacks discuss Trump’s continued disregard for safety precautions, what the latest polling and campaign ad buys tell us about the state of the race, and the Hacks make their first and highly anticipated electoral college predictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:10:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856235.mp3?modified=1619789288&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Welcome to Fiasco Season 1 Bush v. Gore</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Host Leon Neyfakh transports listeners into the day-to-day reality of our country’s most pivotal historical events, bringing to life the forgotten twists and turns of the past while shedding light on the present. &lt;em&gt;Fiasco&lt;/em&gt; season 1 takes listeners to the contested 2000 election between Al Gore and George W. Bush, and the extraordinary legal battle that unfolded in Florida. Fiasco is a Luminary original. To hear other seasons, go to &lt;a href="http://luminarypodcasts.com"&gt;luminarypodcasts.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856236.mp3?modified=1619789179&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Final Debate: Mr. Mute vs. Sir Scranton</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy sit down after the final presidential debate, accompanied by some chips and guac, for a late-night edition of snacks-on-tap. The Hacks discuss the night’s biggest moments and whether, with 11 days to go until the election, the debate made an impact on the race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 08:36:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856237.mp3?modified=1619789306&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Polls Traumatic Stress Disorder (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With two weeks to go until Election Day, John Heilemann of Showtime’s The Circus is back to help Axe and Murphy break down the latest national polls, Trump’s closing strategy (or lack thereof), and to preview the final debate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 23:49:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856238.mp3?modified=1619789321&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Crazy Uncle POTUS (with Mark Salter)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Gibbs are joined by Mark Salter, longtime political advisor to the late Senator John McCain and author of a new book The Luckiest Man: Life with John McCain. The Hacks recap the dueling town halls, Trump’s inability to change the narrative, and whether a return to the days of “country first” conservatism is possible. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 23:02:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856239.mp3?modified=1619789321&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Repeat After Me: It's Not 2016 (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amy Walter, the national editor of the Cook Political Report, joins Murphy and Gibbs to discuss the impact of the Supreme Court confirmation hearings and the state of the 2020 Presidential race (yup, you guessed it, it’s stable). Together, they also walk through the most important Senate races we are all talking about to determine who will control the chamber in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856240.mp3?modified=1619789358&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pencesplaining &amp; Insect Baiting</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy are abuzz with post-debate analysis as they convene for a special late night edition of Hacks on Tap. They break down the night’s biggest moments and discuss whether, in a tumultuous week for the 2020 race, this moved the needle in any way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 07:44:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856241.mp3?modified=1619789277&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Cluster on Steroids (with Claire McCaskill)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Missouri Senator Claire McCaskill joins Axe and Murphy to discuss the physical and metaphorical clusters surrounding President Trump. The Hacks attempt to make sense of Trump’s return to the White House after a brief stay at Walter Reed, unpack the latest polling numbers, and the Senator offers advice for her former colleagues on how Democrats should navigate the impending hearings for Trump’s Supreme Court pick.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 22:36:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856242.mp3?modified=1619789303&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacks on Call</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The news that President Trump tested positive for Coronavirus has thrown the campaign—and the country—into a new realm of uncertainty. Axe, Gibbs, and Murphy convene for a special edition of Hacks on Tap to discuss this breaking news and what it means for the presidential race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856243.mp3?modified=1619789313&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Who Is "They" And Where Is This River? (with Charlie Sykes)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Gibbs spend this episode talking to The Bulwark's Charlie Sykes and in search of this river! Two days after the Cleveland Debacle we sift through the debate one more time, talk about the politics of the economy and ask Charlie about what's happening in his state of Wisconsin. We're still wondering who is they and, yes, we'll keep looking for the river.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 04:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856244.mp3?modified=1619789486&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>$h!t Show</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs convene after the first presidential debate to discuss the perfectly polite and productive national conversation we just witnessed. What are the implications for the race moving forward? How does this impact the VP debate next week? Has the shouting ended? The Hacks break down all this and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 09:12:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856245.mp3?modified=1619789397&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's Peaceful Transfer of Glower (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Murphy and Gibbs welcome the Honorable Hack/former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel to talk about Trump’s comments on election rigging, what Biden has to do in the upcoming debate next week and more politics around the Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856246.mp3?modified=1619789400&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>SCOTUS Scramble (with Bob Shrum)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined this week by Bob Shrum, longtime political consultant, speechwriter, and strategist. The Hacks discuss the politics of the Supreme Court vacancy and what this means for Republicans’ chances of keeping the majority in the Senate. Plus, with one week to go before the first presidential debate, the Hacks break down what both Biden and Trump must achieve in this critical first encounter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:56:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856247.mp3?modified=1619789428&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Lowering the Barr</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe is joined by John Heilemann of Showtime’s The Circus, and Matthew Dowd, Chief Political Analyst at ABC and former chief strategist for the Bush 2004 campaign. The Hacks discuss Attorney General Bill Barr’s eye-popping assertions, the politics of a COVID vaccine, and the latest installment of Democratic bedwetting about Biden’s campaign strategy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:25:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856248.mp3?modified=1619789436&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Mellman College of Polling Knowledge (with Mark Mellman)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You got a polling question? Well, we got your answer! Murphy and Gibbs tap the voluminous knowledge and experience of super pollster Mark Mellman on battleground states, Latino voters, undecided voters, debate polling bumps, third party voters, how a poll is conducted and…ok, you get the point!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 23:47:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856249.mp3?modified=1619789447&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Playing It Down With Bob</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gibbs and Murphy are joined by guest hack Joe Trippi. In this episode, they talk about Trump’s 18 (!!!) interviews with Bob Woodward, the polling anxiety that goes with being a Democrat and winning Senate seats in tough political territory in 2020. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 05:47:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856250.mp3?modified=1619789424&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Coward in Chief (with Stephanie Cutter)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined by Stephanie Cutter, a longtime Democratic operative who most recently produced the 2020 Democratic National Convention. They discuss the Atlantic’s reporting that Trump made disparaging remarks about the military, how the Trump campaign squandered its huge cash advantage, and what the Biden campaign must do in the lead-up to the first debate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:51:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856251.mp3?modified=1619789449&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>An Election So Nice, You’ll Want to Vote Twice! (With Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gibbs and Axe are joined by the one and only Mark McKinnon, co-host of Showtime’s The Circus and a former Presidential advisor to George W. Bush, who spent the week in the battleground state of Wisconsin. We cover the plethora of new national and state polling and talk about where the race stands 60 days before the 2020 election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 03:58:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856252.mp3?modified=1619789463&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Post-Convention Politics &amp; The Dark Force Farce</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined this week by Addisu Demissie, former campaign manager for Cory Booker’s presidential run and senior advisor for Joe Biden and the DNC. With both national conventions in the rear view mirror, a new phase of the 2020 presidential campaign has begun. The Hacks discuss Trump’s continued law and order strategy, the efficacy of Biden’s condemnation of violence and destruction, and how voters in critical swing states are interpreting the pageant of democracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:18:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856253.mp3?modified=1619789501&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Introducing: It Was Said (w Jon Meacham)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;It Was Said&lt;/em&gt;, a 10-episode limited documentary series looking back on some of the most powerful, impactful and timeless speeches in American history. Join Pulitzer Prize winning and best-selling author-historian, Jon Meacham, Peabody-nominated C13Originals Studios and HISTORY, as we take you through 10 speeches. Season One of &lt;em&gt;It Was Said&lt;/em&gt; draws on a selection of speeches from powerful figures in history like Martin Luther King, Jr., Ronald Reagan, JFK, RFK, Barack Obama, Hillary Clinton, John Lewis, Edward R. Murrow, and Barbara Jordan. Meacham will offer expert insight and analysis into their origins, the orator, the context of the times they were given, why they are still relevant today, and the importance of never forgetting them. Each episode of this documentary podcast series will also bring together some of the top historians, authors and journalists relevant to each respective speech and figure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856254.mp3?modified=1619789413&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's Never Ending Reality Show (With Amanda Carpenter)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Guest Hack Amanda Carpenter of CNN and The Bulwark joins Gibbs and Murphy to recap the Trump National Convention. Did the GOP move the needle? What's the next move for Biden and Harris? Is Trump ever going to finish this speech?! The Hacks meticulously dissect the four day reality show and talk about what to expect over the next 67 days of Campaign 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:44:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856255.mp3?modified=1619789460&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>MAGA Mission: The RNC Begins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Guest Hack John Heilemann of Showtime's The Circus is back this week to help Axe and Murphy recap the first night of the Republican National Convention. The GOP promised a week full of optimism and opportunity; after night one, did they deliver? The Hacks discuss whether the first night offered a glimpse of the Republican primary in 2024, if the RNC will ultimately succeed in expanding Trump's base, and what Biden's campaign must do to counter the messaging coming out of the RNC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 23:07:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856256.mp3?modified=1619789493&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>DNC Recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With our new Hackaroo host Robert Gibbs at the helm, Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs recap the Democratic National Convention. After an eventful week which culminated in Joe Biden officially accepting the Democratic nomination for president, the guys discuss their biggest takeaways. Did the Democrats accomplish what they set out to do? How will the Republicans respond next week? Plus, will traditional, funny hat-clad conventions ever return? Tune in to find out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 07:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856257.mp3?modified=1619789487&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Conventions Commence (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The day after the debut of the first-ever virtual convention, Axe and Murphy convene to discuss what worked and what didn’t. Joined by former Chicago mayor Rahm Emanuel, the Hacks break down the messaging, strategy, and tactics used throughout the first night of the Democratic National Convention. They also take listener questions about how convention speakers are selected, what the future holds for House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, and how Trump might impact down-ballot races. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856258.mp3?modified=1619789500&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Executive Disorder (with Paul Begala)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are reunited this week and joined by Paul Begala, former counselor to President Clinton and author of the new book, "You're Fired: The Perfect Guide to Beating Donald Trump." The Hacks convened before Biden announced his choice of Senator Kamala Harris as his running mate, but that doesn't mean we can't include one final round of veepstakes. We also discuss the Trump campaign's renewed line of attack on Biden and assess whether it's an effective strategy, the President's executive orders, the future of the Republican party, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856259.mp3?modified=1619789527&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>It's Harris!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The veepstakes are finally over and the pick is in: Joe Biden has chosen Senator Kamala Harris as his running mate! In this special addition of Hacks on Tap, Axe, Murphy, and guest Hack Robert Gibbs discuss what went into this decision and what it means for Biden’s chances in November.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856260.mp3?modified=1619789477&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Where’s the Manual for Mayhem?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Murphy is out on assignment this week, but thankfully Alex Wagner and Robert Gibbs are here to fill the void. The Hacks discuss Trump’s unrelenting attacks on mail-in voting and his attempts to undermine institutions like the Post Office that are vital to the election; the strategy—or lack thereof—behind granting sit-down interviews with the President; the latest speculation about Biden’s VP pick; and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856261.mp3?modified=1619789560&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>VP Jeebies (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week we’re joined by super Hack John Heilemann, co-host of &lt;em&gt;The Circus&lt;/em&gt; on Showtime. It’s no secret that one of Trump’s biggest obstacles to reelection is his own handling of the COVID-19 pandemic. What, if anything, can he do to make up ground before November? And with time running out for Biden to announce his VP pick, will he make a head or a heart decision? Plus, the recent polls are good news for Biden, but are Democrats too complacent? The Hacks discuss all this and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856262.mp3?modified=1619789559&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Fort Bragg-adocious (with Donna Brazile)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined this week by Democratic political strategist and former acting DNC Chair Donna Brazile. We talk about Trump’s new interview with Fox’s Chris Wallace, POTUS’s alternative reality strategy, and the Confederate-named military base controversy. We also assess the politics of the Democratic and Republican conventions, talk VP selection stakes, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856263.mp3?modified=1619789555&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Cognitive Distancing (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined by guest hack Mark McKinnon, former presidential adviser and co-host of Showtime’s The Circus. This week we talk Trump’s continuous Covid catastrophe, presidential ad wars, Roger Stone on the loose, Veepstakes, and more. We also answer listener questions on Trump and race, presidential debates, and third-party advertising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856264.mp3?modified=1619789554&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Chaos Culture and a Special Senate Deep-Dive (with Amy Walter)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks return for a special Senate deep-dive with The Cook Political Report’s Amy Walter. First, we talk Trump’s new ad offensive, the torqued up grievance war, and how it may play in the 2020 presidential race. We turn to the Senate and assess the most competitive races: vulnerable seats, Republicans in trouble, and the likeliest blue-to-red flips. When will it be time for down-ballot Republicans to distance themselves from Trump? And can they — or is Trump too hard to dump?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:36:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856265.mp3?modified=1619789579&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Pandemic Panic: Trump’s COVID Crack-Up (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week the Hacks welcome back John Heilemann of Showtime’s &lt;em&gt;The Circus &lt;/em&gt;and The Recount. We cover Covid's resurgence in red states and how it could affect Trump’s reelection bid, mixed messaging from the White House, Trump’s reckoning with race relations, new swing state polling, how Trump-Biden debates could impact the election, and more. We also answer listener questions on competitive Senate races, what the conventions might look like, and what advice we might give to those who might want to jump in to politics and lend a hand to campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:03:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856266.mp3?modified=1619789567&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Tirades in Tulsa (with Robert Gibbs)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by former White House press secretary Robert Gibbs. We talk Trump’s Tulsa tirade and what the smaller-than-anticipated crowd size could mean for the campaign, the administration’s ongoing bungled pandemic response, big obstacles for Biden, the Bolton book, and more. Plus, we answer listener questions on whether a national crisis changes the importance of the economy in the minds of voters, to what extent we can trust polls this year, and Susan Rice VP speculation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 23:51:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856267.mp3?modified=1619789509&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The President of Lawlessness and Disorder (with Alex Wagner)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined this week by Alex Wagner of Showtime’s “The Circus” and CBS News.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trumpworld is in turmoil as civil rights protests churn nationwide, POTUS’s poll numbers plunge, and the Supreme Court hands down a landmark pro-LGBTQ decision penned by Trump appointee Neil Gorsuch. The Hacks talk through what this means for Trump’s electoral prospects and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, we discuss statewide polling and competitive Senate races, and answer listener mailbag questions on whether anything Trump does can turn his base against him, AG Barr and the potential for blanket pardons, and which media markets Team Biden should prioritize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:29:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856268.mp3?modified=1619789565&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Protests, Polling, and Provisions (with Phil Rosenthal)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Joining Murphy at the helm this week is Phil Rosenthal, television writer, producer, and creator of Netflix’s “Somebody Feed Phil.” This week, we talk Trump’s plummeting approval rating amid nationwide protests, what Joe Biden needs to do to from now until November, what the latest polling could portend for the general election, and more. We also talk about the politics of food and how a meal can bring people together, especially on the campaign trail. Finally, Murphy answers listener questions on closed party primaries and which states might the likeliest bellwethers on election night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856269.mp3?modified=1619789568&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Nation Grieves and the President Seethes (with Robert Gibbs)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined this week by former Obama White House press secretary Robert Gibbs. We discuss the grief and outrage gripping the nation in the wake of George Floyd’s murder, the suppression of peaceful protestors at Trump’s behest, how the politics of the moment have shifted, Joe Biden’s attempt to take the wheel, and more. The Hacks also take listener’s questions about Trump’s relationship with Twitter, the youth vote, and what polls portend for Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:09:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856270.mp3?modified=1619789587&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Masks and Gaffes (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined by guest hack John Heilemann of The Recount and Showtime’s &lt;em&gt;The Circus&lt;/em&gt;. This week we unpack the latest polling, what the Hacks think might move persuadable voters, Biden’s most recent gaffe and how it might impact the veepstakes, convention apprehension, and more. Plus, we answer listener questions on campaign strategy, Arizona's potential to flip from red to blue, and the likelihood of Trump swapping out VP Pence for Nikki Haley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856271.mp3?modified=1619789643&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>POTUS’s Prescription: Hoaxes and Hydroxy (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Guest hack Rahm Emanuel, former Chicago mayor and Chief of Staff to President Obama, joins Axe and Murphy to discuss Trump’s trip down hydroxychloroquine lane, the Democratic party’s messaging problem, ‘Obamagate,’ and more. Plus, Axe, Murphy, and Rahm answer listener questions on Trump’s teflon approval ratings, the effectiveness of negative campaign ads, and what young people can do to get involved in politics and public service.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856272.mp3?modified=1619789535&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Prevailin’ or Just Wailin’? (with Robert Gibbs)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy are joined this week by Robert Gibbs, former White House press secretary. This week we talk Trump’s tantrum press briefing, Obama’s criticism of the federal government’s response to COVID-19, the state of various Senate races, and more. The Hacks also answer listener questions on the odds that Michelle Obama returns to the political arena and why betting markets often differ from the polls &lt;strong&gt;— &lt;/strong&gt;and which to believe.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 22:34:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856273.mp3?modified=1619789543&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Ain't No Abe Lincoln (with Alex Wagner)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are joined this week by Alex Wagner, host of Crooked Media’s new podcast “Six Feet Apart” and co-host of Showtime’s &lt;em&gt;The Circus. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We talk Trump’s pivot from running &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; the economy to running &lt;em&gt;from&lt;/em&gt; the economy, and the wild comparison he made between himself and President Lincoln. The Hacks also discuss Axe &amp;amp; David Plouffe’s New York Times op-ed in which they give advice to Team Biden, developments in the Tara Reade sexual assault allegations, and the state of play in competitive Senate races.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Axe, Murphy, and Wagner sift through the mail bag and answer listeners’ questions on the potential impact of Justin Amash’s third-party bid, a possible drawback in selecting a sitting governor as Biden’s VP, and what kind of role Trump might play in the Republican Party after his presidency comes to an end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 01:39:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856274.mp3?modified=1619789558&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump Derails and Clorox Cocktails (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy reunite this week with special guest hack John Heilemann of MSNBC, The Recount, and Showtime’s The Circus. The Hacks talk Trump’s China blame game and the politics of the economy. Plus, they discuss what Biden can and should be doing to define himself in the campaign—so Trump doesn't do it for him. Finally, they take listeners’ questions on the Veepstakes, Mike Bloomberg’s war chest, and Democratic populism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856275.mp3?modified=1619789566&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Open Mic Night and Gov Fights (with Mark McKinnon)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy unite virtually with guest hack Mark McKinnon, former presidential adviser and co-host of Showtime’s The Circus.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week, we talk POTUS’ push to re-open the economy, the latest general election polling and what it could portend for November. We also break down Biden’s new ad and debate whether news networks should air Trump’s daily press briefings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we sort through the mail bag and answer listeners’ questions on Elizabeth Warren as a potential vice presidential pick, why Murphy and McKinnon don’t consider Trump a conservative, and which political movies the Hacks deem their favorites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:04:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856276.mp3?modified=1619789573&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's Total Authority (with Rahm Emanuel)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy return with fellow super-hack and former Chicago mayor Rahm Emanuel to talk all the latest, including Trump’s presser meltdown, Obama’s Biden endorsement, the Wisconsin election, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We reach into the mail bag and take listeners’ questions on Biden’s vice presidential pick, Trump’s removal of the Coronavirus fund watchdog, and what happens if Trump refuses to leave office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 02:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856277.mp3?modified=1619789576&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump’s Prescription: Mixed Messaging</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are once again joined by former White House Press Secretary Robert Gibbs to break down the latest in a raucous week in DC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin improbably held its primary amid a pandemic, despite the governor’s attempt to postpone it. Could this set a precedent for November?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Axe, Murphy, and Gibbs discuss the ousting of yet another White House press secretary and what this means for the administration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, they discuss the probability of a virtual convention and what more, if anything, the Biden campaign should be doing right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tune in to hear all this and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856278.mp3?modified=1619789591&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Reality vs. A Reality Show</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy are joined by former Obama White House Press Secretary Robert Gibbs to discuss the latest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When reality becomes reality TV: Trump’s daily press briefings threaten to sweep reality under the rug in a barrage of disinformation. Is Trump’s tactic an effective one?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where’s Joe?—In the throes of a pandemic, it seems impossible for Biden to forge a platform of his own. Could Biden's empathetic message be seen as the antidote to Trump, or will the general election simply be a referendum on the president?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hacks dive beneath the toplines in new polling from the Washington Post and Fox News—what might these breakdowns tell us about turnout patterns in 2020?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Murphy, Axe, and Gibbs reach into the mail bag and field listeners’ questions on whether free market health care works, gubernatorial leadership, and the potential for election postponement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856279.mp3?modified=1619789589&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Crisis of Confidence</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The socially-distanced Hacks reunite virtually to discuss the latest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump twists his tune as the dire COVID-19 consequences take hold. Trump is zeroing in on the pandemic’s economic impact, but will this messaging be effective, and is it smart?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biden’s buzz abates as coronavirus coverage rightfully continues to dominate news cycles. Axe and Murphy put on their campaign hats and offer strategic advice for the presumptive Democratic nominee: how should he position himself during a nationwide crisis of confidence? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the Hacks tackle listeners’ questions on whether they think Trump will use the pandemic as an excuse to dodge debates with Biden, and whether reporters should be more aggressive during press briefings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 22:50:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856280.mp3?modified=1619789593&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>“I’m dealing with a #$%*ing global crisis” (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The socially-distanced Hacks reunite with special guest John Heilemann of MSNBC, Showtime’s &lt;em&gt;The Circus&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;The Recount. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the gravity of the Coronavirus escalates and the world shudders to a halt, where do we go from here? What does it mean for what’s left of the Democratic primary and beyond?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the wake of another round of primaries on Tuesday, Bernie’s chance at nabbing the nomination dwindles even further. Will he bow out any time soon, and what becomes of his loyal base?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reality cuts through the bubble of bull%^&amp;amp;*: from fanning conspiracies last week to a ‘wartime’ stature this week, President Trump pivots on the pandemic. As markets crash and the global economy collapses, what will this mean for him politically? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the Hacks-plus-Heilemann dive into the mailbag and answer listeners’ questions on how Biden overcame organizational weaknesses, Bernie and Warren’s fight for the Left, VP Pence’s role as virus czar, and voter turnout trends. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856281.mp3?modified=1619789600&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Debate, Uncharted Waters, and the Veepstakes Begin</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks convene the day after what might be the last debate of the primary to share their reactions and analysis. What did Biden and Sanders do well and where did they miss the mark? Will Biden’s promise to choose a woman as his running mate change the game? And with COVID-19 rightfully dominating the news, where does the race go from here? Tune in to hear the latest from Hacks on Tap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 22:54:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856282.mp3?modified=1619789596&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Bern Cools and Politics of a Pandemic</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Another Super Tuesday is behind us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bernie Sanders makes it clear he intends to stay in the race — for now. What does this mean for the upcoming head-to-head debate in Arizona?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What message does Biden need to send to Sanders’ supporters in order to gain their support?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Axe and Murphy dive into the data from last night's contests to see what, if anything, the turnout may portend for the general election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, the Hacks talk politics of the Coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also take listeners' questions on the newfangled wave of support for Joe Biden and why some candidates seem more "likable" when they drop out of the race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tune in!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:48:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856283.mp3?modified=1619789591&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Super Tuesday Recap: And Then There Were Two</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Turns out Super Tuesday was super exciting. The Hacks spent a day taking it all in and are now ready to sort through the fallout. Where did Biden’s surprise surge come from? Now that the race has narrowed to two, what’s the path forward for both candidates? Are the Democrats still facing the prospect of a contested convention? Plus, Axe and Murphy open the mail bag to take listeners’ questions. Tune in to hear all this and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:34:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856284.mp3?modified=1619789603&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Fact of the Matter is… Joe is Back!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks convene in the aftermath of the South Carolina Democratic primary to talk about what Joe Biden’s win might mean for the rest of the race. Did Biden get his Mo-Joe back?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buttigieg drops out — does this portend the end for Klobuchar and Warren as well?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And what should we be looking for on Super Tuesday?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...All this and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 02:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856285.mp3?modified=1619789596&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>BONUS: How To Vote for the Next President</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this bonus crossover episode, the Hacks join Slate's "How To! With Charles Duhigg" to discuss how to weigh ideology vs. electability and rank the issues that really matter. They talk to an Independent voter who hasn't made up his mind. Can their advice help Anthony—and all of us—make sure our vote counts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Released February 25, 2020. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856286.mp3?modified=1619789651&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Will the Democratic Party Bern?—On to South Carolina</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back for a special post-Nevada, pre-South Carolina pod:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, Sanders claims his surge has the Democratic establishment worried: can anyone best Bernie or will the Democratic socialist nab the nomination? And what might a Sanders nomination mean for down-ballot races?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of Bloomberg's paltry debate performance remains to be seen, but may spell trouble for the billionaire. Will another media blitz move the needle for the former mayor?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we turn the corner on Nevada and steer to South Carolina, and all eyes are on Joe Biden: will the former Vice President pick up the Joe-mentum he needs or will his debate performance sink expectations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And in Washington: Donald Trump fires the Acting Director of National Intelligence and appoints the U.S. Ambassador to Germany in his wake. But how much do voters really care about the chaos?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the Hacks dive into our mail bag and take listeners’ questions on whether Bloomberg should launch a media assault on Bernie, and how some candidates’ debate prep failed to gird them for the obvious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:15:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856287.mp3?modified=1619789605&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Sin City Slugfest: Democrats Duke it Out</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back to break down the latest Democratic debate from Las Vegas, Nevada–&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike Bloomberg makes his debate stage debut but bombs under a barrage of blows. He may have fallen short on the debate stage at the hands of Elizabeth Warren and others, but will his incoming ad blitzes erase his paltry performance? Plus, Pete Buttigieg takes some of the wind out of Klobuchar’s sails, but will this muddle in the middle ultimately benefit Bernie?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where are we now? As we lurch toward Super Tuesday, the possibility of a brokered convention seems more real than ever before. What does this mean for the party – and for Democratic prospects against Donald Trump? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And no Holds Barr-ed: the Hacks dive into the chaos from the Justice Department and touch on Trump’s pardon-palooza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:03:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856288.mp3?modified=1619789610&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Live Free or Die: New Hampshire Votes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back to break down the results out of New Hampshire. Bernie Sanders narrowly edged out Pete Buttigieg in the first in the nation primary. Amy Klobuchar proved that the “Klobusurge” is real after a strong debate performance propelled her to a third place finish in New Hampshire. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we look towards Nevada and beyond, what do the results from the first two contests mean for Joe Biden and Elizabeth Warren? What do Buttigieg and Klobuchar need to do to continue their momentum in the lead up to Super Tuesday? And with Mike Bloomberg making his debate debut next week, is his path to the nomination suddenly becoming more clear?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hacks also open up the mail bag and give shout outs to some of their favorite books on the behind-the-scenes of campaign strategery. Finally, they bid adieu to candidates who decided New Hampshire was the end of the road for their campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 20:46:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856289.mp3?modified=1619789616&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Quality (Out-of) Control: Iowa’s Meltdown and On to New Hampshire</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Bleary-eyed and results-less, Murphy and guest hack Robert Gibbs join forces to wade through last night’s Iowa caucus madness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are the Iowa caucuses no longer viable? Laden with technical difficulties and “quality control” issues, was the mangled process the nail in the coffin for Iowa’s first-in-the-nation status? Or for caucuses in general?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the country holds its breath, multiple candidates seize on the opportunity to tout a “victory” speech: to what degree is the real winner’s spotlight diluted? If Buttigieg wins Iowa, but doesn't get to enjoy a big bounce going into New Hampshire, what will it mean for his candidacy? Will Biden crumble if he underperforms expectations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And on impeachment: Murphy shares his take on former client Sen. Lamar Alexander and the Hacks wade through what happens next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, we dive into the mailbag and take listeners’ questions on why Nevada is so often overlooked in the early states' media narrative, and how Murphy feels about the Wall Street Journal’s soft touch on Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 21:04:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856290.mp3?modified=1619789615&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Burisma is the New Benghazi and the Mad Dash to Iowa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back this week with a live edition before students at the University of Chicago Institute of Politics. We talk all the latest—&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, John Bolton’s new book coincidentally coincides with his willingness to testify before the Senate. If he is indeed called as a witness, how much will it matter – if at all? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump defense lawyer Pam Bondi aims her case squarely at the Bidens and Burisma – is Burisma the new Benghazi?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biden, Sanders, Warren, Buttigieg, and Klobuchar vie for the lead in Iowa. With three of the five frontrunners trapped in jury duty, how will the final results take shape? Plus, the Hacks review the latest ads from all five top contenders, sharing their views on how the ad wars could impact each candidate’s position in the race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We take live mail bag questions from students at the University of Chicago, who wonder if there’s room for both Sanders and Warren to split the lead in Iowa. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Last Call this week takes a closer look at a newly-minted Amy Klobuchar ad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 22:35:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856291.mp3?modified=1619789621&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Impeachy Not-So-Keen and the Iowa Countdown</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are here to talk all the latest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The impeachment trial launches in the Senate and both sides assume their marks: will it amount to more than Kabuki theater, or will the partisan paradigm pervade? And how much will it matter in November?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T minus two weeks until our favorite time of the year: the Iowa caucuses! Polling points to cadre of four frontrunners: under what circumstances could any of them pull ahead? And as the Warren/Bernie feud continues to dominate news coverage, who benefits from the spat, and how will it shape the fight to lead the Left?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Klobuchar is climbing in the polls: but will Senate jury duty hamper her chances? Is there a lane for Mayor Mike Bloomberg under any circumstances?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hacks dive into the mailbag: we offer advice to an Iowa caucus voter and assess the possibility that Team Warren planted the Bernie bout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the New York Times’ editorial board offer their endorsement to an unprecedented two Democratic contenders. What say the Hacks about this anomalous assertion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 20:14:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856292.mp3?modified=1619789624&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Duking it Out in Des Moines and the Non-Handshake from Hell</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The mad dash to the Iowa caucuses are upon us! The Hacks break down the Des Moines Register/CNN Democratic Debate—and pinch-hitting for David this week is the great Robert Gibbs, former White House Press Secretary under President Obama. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hacks tackle Iowa: it’s a race to the finish as four leading candidates vie for the top spot. Gibbs and Murphy draw from their experiences as former campaign pros to dish behind-the-scenes info on the Iowa caucuses. Can caucus procedure shape the outcome? And a chunk of Hawkeye voters still remain undecided: will this shake up the race?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Democrats duke it out in Des Moines: Bernie and Warren plunge into a cold war, culminating in the “non-handshake from hell” – will it impact Bernie’s strong standing in the polls? Biden stood his ground, but will it be enough? Buttigieg and Klobuchar try to claim the centrist torch: is it strong enough to knock Biden from his perch?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The articles of impeachment have been transmitted from the House to the Senate: will new evidence and potential new witnesses shape the outcome? And will the presidential contenders on Senate “jury duty” suffer from absences in Iowa? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the Hacks dive into the mailbag and take listeners’ questions on the possibility and outcome of a brokered convention, whether or not Iowa has the potential to fall to Democrats in the general election, and the extent to which Trump has hijacked the Republican Party. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:12:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856293.mp3?modified=1619789632&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacky New Year!—Iran, Iowa, &amp; Impeachment</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks kick off the new decade with all the latest—&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President Trump ordered the fatal strike of Iranian Gen. Qassem Soleimani last week. Was there a strategy behind the move, and to what end? Will the attack play to his base or undermine his pledge to end endless war? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Bolton says he’ll testify before the Senate during the President’s impeachment trial. But will it move the needle in the Senate?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Iowa caucuses are upon us! With a purported three-way tie between Biden, Buttigieg, and Bernie – and Warren not far behind – the frontrunners vie for victory. What do the latest fundraising disclosures mean for the candidates and their campaigns, and how will it shake up the final weeks of the Iowa race?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hacks also tackle listener questions on how likely a repeat PA, MI, and WI general election sweep is for President Trump, and share a Hacks history lesson – when and how Axe and Murphy, political pros hailing from opposite sides of the aisle, became pod-mates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 21:16:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856294.mp3?modified=1619789630&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Merry Debate-mas with a Dash of Joe-mentum</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks reunite in Los Angeles, California as the sixth Democratic debate draws to a close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden and Amy Klobuchar overperform the norm: will this newfound Joe-mentum last?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The blows buffet Buttigieg: will he weather the storm?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We turn to impeachment: the House of Representatives voted this week to impeach Donald Trump, but his approval rating remains steady. How will the saga unfold, and what will it portend for the 2020 election?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this and more during our midnight edition of Hacks on Tap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 09:54:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856295.mp3?modified=1619789623&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Jolt’n Joe Biden and Impeachment Day Zero</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The hacks are here to talk all the latest— &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Politics of impeachment: as the impeachment saga continues to unfold, Democrats and Republicans alike continue to politicize the process. How much — if at all — will this weaken Trump in 2020, and will any senators defect from the party line? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone had his Cup o’ Joe! Biden talks tough toward an Iowa voter — did he cross the line, or is this the energy voters want to see from him? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg’s bid: he’s flush with cash and flooding the airwaves—but will he make a splash? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, we dive into the mailbag and answer listeners’ questions on what the onslaught of House GOP retirements mean, how to reconcile Buttigieg’s Christian faith with his lack of support among faith-based strongholds, and parse through what the “white working class” actually means. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856296.mp3?modified=1619789628&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>26: No Kamalot! Harris Exits and Trump Churns</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, the Hacks dive into the latest polling out of New Hampshire and size up the state of the race. With the breaking news that Sen. Kamala Harris is dropping out, will other lower-tier candidates follow suit? Is Bloomberg’s huge ad buy cash well-spent, or will he fail to break through? Will Mayor Pete’s weekend jaunt through the Carolinas move the needle? Plus, Axe and Murphy talk Trump’s visit to the NATO summit and dig into the latest impeachment news. Tune in for all this and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856297.mp3?modified=1619789625&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Great Zzzzebate and Will Impeachment Ignite?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back to discuss the latest Democratic debate. With public impeachment hearings sucking up most of the oxygen, did the debate move the needle in the race? Axe and Murphy break down each candidate’s performance and recap the night’s best—and worst—moments. The Hacks also weigh in on the latest impeachment news. Despite some extraordinary testimony, will the Senate vote to convict? Tune in to hear Axe and Murphy’s take!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856298.mp3?modified=1619789640&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Bloomberg or Iceberg?—New Entrants and The Impeachment Show</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks huddle to tackle the latest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The public impeachment hearings kick off this week. Republicans have been auditioning wild arguments in defense of the president—and Jeff Sessions’ new Senate ad suggests this won’t change—what, if anything, will bring Republicans around? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Former Massachusetts governor Deval Patrick and former NYC mayor Michael Bloomberg consider throwing their hats into the Democratic race. Will it spark a Deval-ution or fail to bloom?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pete Buttigieg surges in Iowa but is starting to take fire from Amy Klobuchar and Elizabeth Warren. Will the hits stick, and what does it mean for the young mayor?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the Hacks take listeners’ questions on how Trump may affect down-ballot races, the potential power of a unity ticket, and why TV ads matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856299.mp3?modified=1619789642&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Poltergeisty Polls, LJ Dinner Wrap-Up, and Bye-Bye Beto</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back this week to talk through the latest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The famed Liberty and Justice Dinner (formerly known as the Jefferson-Jackson) wrapped last Friday in Iowa: Who stood out, what does it mean, and how much will it shake up the race?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Poll-a-palooza: Why do Axe and Murphy dub the slew of new polls in early swing states a “wake-up call” for Dems?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State of the Senate: a growing number of Republican senators consider acknowledging Trump's misdeeds with Ukraine—but does it matter?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…And we raise our glasses to Beto O’Rourke for a hard-fought bid for the nomination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hacks close with listeners’ mailbag questions on why internal polls matter and the potential impact of a third-party candidate on the race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856300.mp3?modified=1619789645&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>al-Baghdadi Issues and Impressions in Iowa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, the Hacks talk politics of al-Baghdadi: did Trump overplay the death of the ISIS leader? Will Trump benefit, and will it last? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timing of Nancy Pelosi's impeachment decision strikes Axe and Murphy as peculiar: Why now? What does it mean for 2020?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden's new 60 Minutes interview featured the side of Biden everyone's been waiting for. Is the former Veep's 'Candidate Protection Program' turning over a new leaf? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, the Hacks talk Nate Silver's new FiveThirtyEight story on whether or not Democrats really want a new candidate, the politics of Biden's PAC reversal, and the upcoming Law and Justice (formerly known as the Jefferson-Jackson) dinner in Iowa, the event that was considered a launchpad for President Obama. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hacks wrap by answering listeners' questions on whether or not Murphy can be convinced to vote for Liz Warren, and whether it's better to be leading in national polls or gaining in statewide polls. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856301.mp3?modified=1619789637&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>The Pierre Affair and Senate Slippage? (with Cory Booker)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, the Hacks dive into: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The state of the Senate Republicans: Is Mitt Romney — aka Pierre Delecto — a lone detractor of harbinger of what’s to come? Plus, Lindsay Graham tells Axios that evidence of a true quid pro quo could change his mind on impeachment, and new data spells potential trouble for some senators up for re-election in 2020. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s out of the frying pan and into the fire for Elizabeth Warren as she continues to be pressed for details on her Medicare for All plan. She’s promised a roadmap in the coming weeks, but could the delay cause problems for the newly-minted frontrunner? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New polling from Iowa is in: will Buttigieg’s bump overcome any growing pains for his campaign? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Sen. Cory Booker joins the Hacks, who ask for his take on Warren’s new education plan, why his poll numbers seem to be lagging in Iowa, and whether or not he seems himself as a good alternative to Biden. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the mail bag returns with answers to why healthcare suddenly seems to be the Democrats’ downfall, if Trump’s social media war chest can overcome his unpopularity, and which if any Democratic candidate has the potential to draw from Biden’s strong support from African-American voters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856302.mp3?modified=1619789649&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>All's Fair in Love and Warren</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The fourth Democratic presidential debate is behind us and the hacks are here to break it all down. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All eyes are on Liz Warren as she gets frontrunner treatment for the very first time: how did she fare? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buttigieg bites back: is this a turning point for the South Bend mayor? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biden becomes background: can his candidacy sustain steam?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy  brought her A-game: but is this too little, too late? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s not working for Cory Booker? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, the hacks dive into what the latest FEC filings mean for each of the candidates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...All this, and much more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856303.mp3?modified=1619789639&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Great and Unmatched... Wisdom (with John Heilemann)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back from their jaunt to Austin and itching to dig into the latest. Hill Republicans and Democrats alike are in a tizzy over Trump’s call to pull troops out of Syria – but will the move resonate with his voting base? Meanwhile the impeachment inquiry has some congressional Republicans wondering if it's time to revolt and bolt. The great John Heilemann joins Axe and Murphy to share intel from the ground in Iowa and lets us in on who he thinks is the dark horse to watch. And finally, the Hacks dive into the mailbag and take listeners’ questions on whether David would trade Obama’s second term for Trump, whether or not Trump has lost Fox News, and impeachment’s potential impact on House and Senate races.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856304.mp3?modified=1619789661&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hacks Live from Austin with Karl Rove</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks reunite LIVE at the Texas Tribune Festival in Austin, TX. This time, they’re joined by super-hack Karl Rove — former Senior Advisor to President George W. Bush — to break down all the latest on the impeachment inquiry, alleged Trump transgressions, the 2020 race, and more. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856305.mp3?modified=1619789774&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hard Rain from Ukraine and Boarding the Bus with Mayor Pete Buttigieg</title><description>&lt;p&gt;From whistleblowers to whistlestops, Axe and Murphy are chewing over the latest call for impeachment, Rep. Joe Kennedy, and new polling out of Iowa. Mayor Pete Buttigieg joins the show from his Not-the-Straight-Talk-Express bus tour of Iowa to give his take on impeachment, what he hears from voters out on the trail, and what sets him apart from the other candidates. In the mailbag, the hacks are talking brokered conventions, young voters, and advice for New Hampshire Never-Trumpers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856306.mp3?modified=1619789752&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>More Debates and 10,000 Takes with Sen. Amy Klobuchar</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back after a Democratic debate with no shortage of talking points: Castro put Biden on blast, Betsy from Oklahoma ditched the cap and gown, and Beto brought the passion on guns. Axe and Murphy also touch on the escalating tensions with Iran over the bombing of a Saudi oil refinery and the latest accusations against Justice Brett Kavanaugh. Senator Amy Klobuchar joins the show to talk about her role in the Kavanaugh hearings and the path forward for her Presidential candidacy. We wrap up with a supersized mailbag with listener questions about the races for the Senate, Biden and the black vote, Mike’s post-Trump journey, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856307.mp3?modified=1619789820&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Houston, We Have a Preview</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hacks are back in the run-up to Thursday’s debate. And the stage in Houston will be packed with TEN candidates—so what does each need to do in order to stand out? In order to keep the cash flowing? In order to maintain top-tier status? In order to avoid getting swallowed-up? Murph and Axe belly-up to the bar and sort through what each campaign’s hacks must be thinking right about now. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 23:29:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856308.mp3?modified=1619789722&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Hats, Prattle, and a Primary Battle with Mark McKinnon</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this week’s episode, Biden flubs the details, but will it ever cross the line with voters? Axe and Murphy also take stock of the rest of the field ahead of the next Democratic debate, what's next for the candidates who didn't make the stage, and Trump's half-hearted hurricane watch. Guest hack Mark McKinnon joins the show to talk about Warren's worries with white working-class and black voters, his affinity for Mayor Pete, and redemption for Beto in Texas. Plus, the hacks hand out a bit of political travel advice for political junkies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856309.mp3?modified=1619789794&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>A Hack in Hog Heaven and Trump’s Tempestuous Trip</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe is back from his stint in the cornfields of Iowa armed with new intel to break down with Murphy. But first – the hacks talk Trump’s erratic behavior at the G7 summit, size up Trump’s new primary challenge from former U.S. Rep. Joe Walsh, pose a theory as to why the governors in the Democratic race have yet to break through, and unpack Axe’s Iowa interviews with the leading presidential candidates. The hacks later dive into the mailbag and answer listener questions on Democratic strategy, to what extent early national polls really matter, and which brews the hacks themselves take on tap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856310.mp3?modified=1619789754&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Mooch Ado About Something</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Axe has returned from his secret mission and is reunited with Murphy as they hash through Trump’s latest poll numbers and his frustration with Fox News. The first Biden TV ad has dropped in Iowa, but does he have what it takes to go the distance? And Anthony Scaramucci joins the Hacks—he’s back in the President’s crosshairs after voicing his opposition to him, and fills us in on his plan to “beat the bully.” He even makes a bit of news on his next steps. Finally the hacks field questions from the mailbag on Iowa’s status as “first in the nation,” and the search for some new and novel ways to campaign against Trump. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856311.mp3?modified=1619789827&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Calling All Conspiracies and Let Biden Be Biden</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this week’s episode, Democratic strategist and guest host Paul Begala joins Murphy on the mic to take stock of this week’s news. The hacks talk Jeffrey Epstein’s sudden death and the rise of conspiracy theories in politics, how Biden could benefit from leaning into his gaffes, and assess the Democratic candidates’ standings in the race. Guest hack and former White House Communications Director Jennifer Palmieri joins the show to share who she thinks has broken through in the Democratic field and her biggest fear for the Democratic Party in 2020. Lastly, the hacks dive into the mailbag and answer listeners’ questions on whether or not Barack Obama could beat Trump, Joaquin Castro taking heat for tweeting names of Trump donors, and the best lane for Mayor Pete in the Democratic race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856312.mp3?modified=1619789763&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Words, Guns, El Paso and Dayton with Rep. Steve Israel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After the country was jolted yet again by mass shootings in El Paso and Dayton, the hacks huddle up to talk about the how the President responded, what we should expect from a "Consoler in Chief," and how some Democratic candidates may set themselves apart as they respond to the tragedies. Former Congressman Steve Israel joins the show to talk about the realities of gun politics, why he hopes this time will be different, as well as his views on the state of the race. Lastly, David and Mike take some questions about "The Loudest Voice," a possible conservative third party, and the politics of health care. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856313.mp3?modified=1619789786&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Showdown in Motown</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this week's episode, the Hacks huddle in Detroit in the wake of the second round of Democratic debates. Axe and Murphy share their takes on the Biden-Harris rematch, discuss the progressive-moderate party divide, highlight Warren and Booker's strong performances, and gauge the impact this round will have on the candidates moving forward. The Hacks also break down the memorable moments: Gabbard takes aim at Harris, Bernie brings the fight, Biden bites back, and a handful of one percenters – Delaney, Bullock, Bennet, and Inslee – make themselves heard. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856314.mp3?modified=1619789779&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>May the debate stage be ever in your favor, Sen. Michael Bennet joins the show</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Axe and Murphy question whether Bob Mueller’s testimony will have any bearing on the race. Then, we’ll preview the Hunger Games, also known as the second round of Democratic debates. It's do or die for candidates stuck at 1%. And, we'll talk to one of those 1 percenters -- Colorado Senator Michael Bennet -- about how he plans to break through and keep the party from "going off a cliff." Plus, we dive into the mailbag to answer questions about the electoral college and whether the Democrats should be doing more to push back against Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856315.mp3?modified=1619789762&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's big trap and who ought to wrap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this week’s episode, Axe and Murphy talk Trump’s strategy behind attacking the progressive freshmen House members, how the latest poll numbers spell potential for Kamala Harris, and whether Pete Buttigieg's coolheaded approach will help or hurt him in the race. Howard Wolfson, former deputy mayor of New York City, joins the show to talk about Michael Bloomberg's decision not to run and what role a third party candidate might play in a general election. Axe and Murphy dive to the mailbag to answer questions about Andrew Yang, Biden's staff, and the art of the post-primary pivot. During "Last Call," both hacks name the candidate they think should drop out of the race sooner rather than later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856316.mp3?modified=1619789805&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Warren's huge haul and Steyer's surprise with Jon Favreau</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, the hacks make sense of the newly announced fundraising numbers, talk Biden’s attempt to relaunch, discuss the political impact of Trump’s flip on the census question, and share their thoughts on Mitch McConnell’s new Senate challenger. Guest hack Jon Favreau of Pod Save America joins the show to talk about billionaire Tom Steyer throwing his hat into the race, the Democratic landscape in a post-debate world, and the rise of left-wing media. Axe and Murphy dive into the mailbag and answer submitted listener questions about what Mayor Pete should do with his impressive fundraising haul and whether or not Trump will participate in the general election debates.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 22:32:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856317.mp3?modified=1619789799&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>5: The post debate pollercoaster and the art of Beto-busting with Julián Castro</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, the hacks throw on their strategists’ caps and discuss how they would manage the leading campaigns in the wake of the first debates. Axe and Murphy also break down the slew of post-debate polling, talk Trump’s trip to North Korea, and discuss whether there’s a lane for a more moderate candidate should Biden’s support continues to slip. Guest hack Julián Castro, former Secretary of Housing and Urban Development and Democratic presidential candidate, joins the show to talk about his standout debate performance, his immigration plan, and what’s next for the campaign. Lastly, the hacks reach into the mailbag and answer listener questions about a Murphy's post-debate advice for Warren, Axe’s take on former Obama staffers working the race, and what Amy Klobuchar needs to do to break through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856318.mp3?modified=1619789808&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>4: Recapping the first Democratic debates</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The first round of debates is in the books. Who helped themselves the most and who's spending their weekend doing damage control? In this bonus episode of Hacks on Tap, Axe and Murphy parse through the winners and losers of the first round of Democratic primary debates. The hacks break down the most memorable moments: Kamala Harris' exchange with Joe Biden, Buttigieg's answer on the South Bend police shooting, Warren's performance as the solo frontrunner onstage night one, Booker's response on gun control, and Castro's potential breakout moment. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856319.mp3?modified=1619789802&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>3: Double-whammy in Miami: First Democratic debate preview</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The hacks talk Biden and Buttigieg’s tough week with race relations [2:52], escalating tensions with Iran [14:48], and preview this week’s Democratic debates [20:14]. Guest hack Stephanie Cutter, deputy campaign manager for President Barack Obama’s 2012 re-election campaign, joins to talk about how each campaign will hope to win the spin game [31:53]. David and Mike also dig into the mail bag , taking listeners’ questions on the electoral college, the relative advantages of the Democratic primary system, and which 2020 Democratic campaign they’d least like to helm [45:17].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856320.mp3?modified=1619789917&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump purging pollsters, Dems ducking digital</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week the hacks talk about President Trump's interview on ABC [1:11], Trump's latest polling prospects [6:20], who was helped and who was hurt by the Democratic debate lottery [14:40], and guest hack David Plouffe joins the show to talk about why Democrats aren't paying more attention to digital advertising while Trump goes all in [18:58]. Finally the hacks open up the mailbag to take a few questions from listeners about bullying, Never-Trumpers, and the importance of the early primary states [33:49].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856321.mp3?modified=1619789902&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>1: Biden plays Hyde and go seek, Warren rising in Iowa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In the inaugural episode of Hacks on Tap, the hacks discuss the latest Democratic poll out of Iowa [1:30], the perils of being frontrunner [6:48], Biden's flip on the Hyde Amendment [10:30], the challenges facing female candidates with guest hack Jennifer Granholm, former governor of Michigan [20:48], Elizabeth Warren's rise [33:02], and Trumps tariff turmoil [35:29]. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856322.mp3?modified=1619789881&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item><item><title>Introduction to Hacks on Tap with David Axelrod and Mike Murphy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Throughout the 2020 presidential campaign, battle-tested operatives will be sitting on bar stools along the trail, sharing war stories and unique, sometimes uproarious cuts on the latest developments. Hacks on Tap is your invitation to join two of the best. Campaign veterans Axelrod and Murphy will take listeners deep inside the top level of American politics. These seasoned pros have seen it all: the peaks and valleys, the pressure-cooker moments, the huge breaks and the horrible calamities no one saw coming. Who better to narrate this momentous race? So pull up a stool and join us every Tuesday afternoon starting on June 11th!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices"&gt;podcastchoices.com/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="http://localhost:8080/process?url=https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/pdst.fm/e/pfx.vpixl.com/ejC8r/clrtpod.com/m/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/7856323.mp3?modified=1619789803&amp;sid=5050689&amp;source=rss" type="audio/mpeg" /></item></channel></rss>